1
00:00:00,138 --> 00:00:02,070
"越狱"前情提要...
Previously on Prison Break...

2
00:00:02,073 --> 00:00:03,573
伊斯兰国的攻击越来越近了
The strikes are getting closer.

3
00:00:03,575 --> 00:00:05,617
我们大概有一天的时间 最多两天
We got a day, maybe two, tops,

4
00:00:05,620 --> 00:00:08,359
-离开这个破地方  -非常时期 非常手段
- to get out of this hole. - Desperate times, desperate measures.

5
00:00:08,362 --> 00:00:09,707
迈克尔在联系我们
Michael's reaching out to us.

6
00:00:09,708 --> 00:00:11,531
我们得寻求帮助 一个叫希巴的女人
We got to get help. A woman named Sheba.

7
00:00:11,530 --> 00:00:13,861
你兄弟在和我们猜谜语啊 是吧
Your brother speaks in riddles, does he?

8
00:00:13,866 --> 00:00:15,320
伊斯兰国 我们得停车了
ISIL. We're gonna get stopped.

9
00:00:15,320 --> 00:00:17,637
为什么不忘记曾经出现在彼此生命里
Why don't we forget each other ever existed.

10
00:00:17,632 --> 00:00:20,380
美人没那么容易被遗忘
Beauty's not so easily forgotten.

11
00:00:20,380 --> 00:00:22,165
巴格威尔 你上面有朋友啊
Friends in high places, Bagwell.

12
00:00:22,160 --> 00:00:25,530
我能帮你装上一副完整的 关节灵活的假肢
I can equip you with a fully articulate prosthetic.

13
00:00:25,530 --> 00:00:26,976
-这是谁安排的  -没有人
- Who's behind this? - Nobody.

14
00:00:26,970 --> 00:00:29,648
-这是坎尼尔·奥提斯  -但你我都清楚
- This is Kaniel Outis. - Okay, but you and I both know

15
00:00:29,642 --> 00:00:31,904
-迈克尔·斯科菲尔德是谁  -我们触发了一些事...
- who Michael Scofield was. - We've awoken something,

16
00:00:31,904 --> 00:00:34,176
一些想被藏起来 跟迈克有关的事
something people are trying to hide about Michael.

17
00:00:34,181 --> 00:00:35,248
雅克布
Jacob?

18
00:00:35,573 --> 00:00:37,340
这就是博弈论
That's game theory. You meet people.

19
00:00:37,350 --> 00:00:38,645
你让他们走进了你的生活
You bring them into your life

20
00:00:38,640 --> 00:00:40,117
直到这一刻
Nuntil the moment

21
00:00:40,117 --> 00:00:41,690
你需要利用这段关系
you need to manipulate the relationship

22
00:00:41,696 --> 00:00:42,630
来获得自己的利益
to your advantage.

23
00:00:42,630 --> 00:00:44,149
你同意帮他... 怎么帮
You agreed to help him... how?

24
00:00:44,149 --> 00:00:45,712
如果我能让监狱断电
If I could arrange a blackout.

25
00:00:45,722 --> 00:00:47,430
他认识一个能帮他逃出去的人
He knew someone who could get him out.

26
00:00:47,435 --> 00:00:49,285
有人找到我爸了
Someone found my father.

27
00:00:49,280 --> 00:00:50,693
那逃跑计划可以开始了
It means the escape is on.

28
00:00:50,693 --> 00:00:52,266
伊斯兰国也下决心
ISIL forces are also bent

29
00:00:52,261 --> 00:00:54,341
要让他们的领袖阿布·拉马尔获释
on freeing their leader Abu Ramal,

30
00:00:54,346 --> 00:00:57,216
他以其极端言行著称
known for his extreme views and practices.

31
00:02:46,660 --> 00:02:49,509
他说是泡泡糖先生给他的
He says Bubble Gum Man sent him.

32
00:02:50,130 --> 00:02:52,074
是个在监狱里的男人 他没见过
Someone in the prison he hasn't met,

33
00:02:52,085 --> 00:02:55,797
但给他泡泡糖让他跑腿
but gives him gum in exchange for errands.

34
00:02:55,808 --> 00:02:57,728
他说他害怕
He says he's frightened.

35
00:02:58,309 --> 00:02:59,810
告诉他没事了
Tell him it's all right.

36
00:02:59,824 --> 00:03:02,496
问问他喜不喜欢嘀嗒糖
Ask him if he does Tic Tacs.

37
00:03:02,853 --> 00:03:04,256
如果他继续传消息的话
He can have the whole lot

38
00:03:04,304 --> 00:03:06,272
整盒都是他的
if he keeps the messages coming.

39
00:03:07,130 --> 00:03:09,390
谢谢你 嘀嗒糖先生
Thank you, Tic Tac Man.

40
00:03:12,677 --> 00:03:15,381
嘀嗒 嘀嗒 嘀嗒
Tic Tac, Tic Tac, Tic Tacs.

41
00:03:16,400 --> 00:03:17,936
这是"古兰经"中的一段
It's a passage from the Suras.

42
00:03:17,940 --> 00:03:19,557
"尤素福对犯人说
"And Yusef said to the prisoner:

43
00:03:19,557 --> 00:03:22,000
'请记得在你主人面前替我申冤'
'Remember me in the presence of your lord.'

44
00:03:22,218 --> 00:03:23,760
"但撒旦让他忘了这件事
"But Satan made him forget,

45
00:03:23,770 --> 00:03:25,034
导致尤素福在监狱里
and Yusef stayed in prison

46
00:03:25,045 --> 00:03:26,853
又多待了几年"
for several years."

47
00:03:27,605 --> 00:03:29,136
笔迹太不正常了
The calligraphy is unusual,

48
00:03:29,136 --> 00:03:31,834
这些空隙 和整个形状
the spacing, the way it's shaped,

49
00:03:32,165 --> 00:03:34,165
像车轮上的辐条
like, like spokes on a wheel.

50
00:03:36,080 --> 00:03:37,776
就像萨那城中心
Like the center of Sana'a.

51
00:03:41,510 --> 00:03:43,696
你觉得他弟弟给了我们一张地图吗
You think his brother sent us a map?

52
00:03:43,776 --> 00:03:45,136
这儿有个红点
There's a red dot

53
00:03:45,178 --> 00:03:46,704
标在"I"旁边
dotting the "I",

54
00:03:47,205 --> 00:03:48,981
不管这儿有什么
and whatever this is here.

55
00:03:49,808 --> 00:03:51,820
他是想给我们一个地点
He's trying to give us a location.

56
00:03:52,000 --> 00:03:53,077
干什么用的地点
A location for what?

57
00:03:53,072 --> 00:03:54,298
我唯一能想到的
The only thing I can think of

58
00:03:54,298 --> 00:03:55,722
就是今晚上越狱后
is where we're supposed to meet him

59
00:03:55,722 --> 00:03:57,472
我们跟他汇合的地点
when the escape goes down tonight.

60
00:04:01,253 --> 00:04:03,109
现在开始 你弟弟的事你自己处理
Your brother is your business now.

61
00:04:03,136 --> 00:04:05,125
我今晚得把我家里人弄上飞机
I have to get my family on a flight tonight

62
00:04:05,130 --> 00:04:06,592
趁机场还没关
before the airport shuts down.

63
00:04:06,613 --> 00:04:07,557
等等
Hold up.

64
00:04:08,000 --> 00:04:09,540
我们也需要票 三张
We need tickets, too, three of them.

65
00:04:09,540 --> 00:04:11,424
一张给我一张是迈克尔的 还有张给他
One for me, one for Michael, one for C.

66
00:04:11,450 --> 00:04:13,866
如果我还能弄到票 那一定是给这些孩子的
If I'm getting anybody any tickets it's these kids,

67
00:04:13,866 --> 00:04:15,157
而不是你那唯利是图的弟弟
not your mercenary brother.

68
00:04:15,157 --> 00:04:17,328
你没钱怎么买票
And how are you going to do that without any money?

69
00:04:20,906 --> 00:04:22,170
你是在拿这些孩子的自由
You're holding these kids' freedom

70
00:04:22,170 --> 00:04:23,888
威胁我 是吗
over my head, is that it?

71
00:04:24,565 --> 00:04:26,880
希巴 你帮我搞到我们的机票
Sheba, you get me those plane tickets,

72
00:04:26,880 --> 00:04:28,512
这些孩子离开这个国家的费用
and I'll pay for every single one of these kids

73
00:04:28,512 --> 00:04:29,925
全部我来付
to get out of this country.

74
00:04:31,248 --> 00:04:34,074
直觉告诉我不管怎样你都会这么做的
Something tells me that's what you want to do anyhow.

75
00:04:34,298 --> 00:04:35,168
小心
Careful.

76
00:04:35,621 --> 00:04:37,738
你在指责我有情有义
You're accusing me of having a heart.

77
00:04:53,480 --> 00:04:56,149
让开 让开
Out of my way. Get out of my way.

78
00:04:56,149 --> 00:04:57,856
怎么 你想打架吗
What, you want to go?

79
00:05:00,256 --> 00:05:01,269
待在一起
Keep it together.

80
00:05:01,264 --> 00:05:03,390
得先在一起才能待在一起啊
You got to have it together to keep it together.

81
00:05:07,050 --> 00:05:08,778
要是这其中一个炸弹打中了我们
One of those hits us now,

82
00:05:09,520 --> 00:05:12,293
-我发誓这一切结束之后...  -9小时
- after all this time, I swear to God... - Nine hours.

83
00:05:12,298 --> 00:05:14,220
9小时我们就能出去了 你明白吗
Nine hours till we get out, you understand?

84
00:05:14,261 --> 00:05:15,465
0点整
00 a.M.

85
00:05:15,460 --> 00:05:17,376
过了今天 我们就能出去了
We get through today and we're on the bricks.

86
00:05:17,381 --> 00:05:18,517
然后呢
And then what?

87
00:05:18,954 --> 00:05:20,620
那是4年前了
It was four years ago.

88
00:05:20,725 --> 00:05:22,790
我们所有的计划 护照啊 那家商店啊
All of our plans, the passports, the shop,

89
00:05:22,790 --> 00:05:25,584
现在这一切有可能都埋在废墟里了
everything is probably under rubble by now.

90
00:05:26,938 --> 00:05:28,620
我让人在处理这些
I got someone on it.

91
00:05:29,890 --> 00:05:31,984
谁 你扔纸飞机的那个小孩子吗
What, the kid you throw planes to?

92
00:05:34,400 --> 00:05:35,493
不
No.

93
00:05:35,493 --> 00:05:38,064
我说的是这个世界上我最信任的人
I'm talking about the only person I trust in the world

94
00:05:38,080 --> 00:05:39,669
就像我相信你一样
as much as I trust you.

95
00:05:41,904 --> 00:05:44,432
就这儿了 这就是地图上的位置
So, this is it, the spot on the map.

96
00:05:44,645 --> 00:05:46,390
店主说四年前他把这家汽车店
The owner says he sold the auto shop

97
00:05:46,390 --> 00:05:47,701
卖给了一个美国人
to an American four years ago

98
00:05:47,706 --> 00:05:49,344
从那以后再也没见过他
and hasn't seen him since.

99
00:06:05,050 --> 00:06:07,178
你知道那个美国人就是迈克尔 对吧
You know that American was Michael, right?

100
00:06:08,117 --> 00:06:10,890
问题是这地方是用来干嘛的
Question is what was he using this place for.

101
00:06:13,093 --> 00:06:14,869
做逃跑计划的
Planning his escape.

102
00:06:19,034 --> 00:06:21,034
看上去他最初的逃跑计划的撤离点
It looks like his original exfil point

103
00:06:21,034 --> 00:06:22,666
是在北部边境
was at the northern border.

104
00:06:22,930 --> 00:06:24,714
现在可办不到了
Won't be doing that now.

105
00:06:24,944 --> 00:06:26,770
是伊斯兰国的地盘了
It's ISIL territory.

106
00:06:29,824 --> 00:06:32,416
实物模型 护照照片
Mock-ups, passport photos,

107
00:06:32,432 --> 00:06:33,786
伪装
disguises.

108
00:06:35,098 --> 00:06:38,202
但好像他没有计划把自己弄出去
But it looks like he just wasn't planning on getting himself out.

109
00:06:38,800 --> 00:06:41,013
他是要把阿布·拉马尔弄出来
He was getting Abu Ramal out.

110
00:06:43,258 --> 00:06:44,490
这家伙是
This guy's the enemy

111
00:06:44,501 --> 00:06:46,826
所有人类文明的敌人 林肯
of everything that's civilized, Linc.

112
00:06:48,858 --> 00:06:50,517
这真的让我怀疑了
That brings me to my real question.

113
00:06:50,512 --> 00:06:52,704
我们他妈到底要救谁出来
Who in the hell are we breaking out?

114
00:06:52,709 --> 00:06:54,272
到底是迈克·斯科菲尔德
Is it Michael Scofield

115
00:06:54,373 --> 00:06:56,224
还是坎尼尔·奥提斯
or Kaniel Outis?

116
00:07:42,880 --> 00:07:44,080
这他妈的怎么了
What the hell's going on?

117
00:07:44,085 --> 00:07:46,810
拉马尔的人要执行伊斯兰教法
Ramal's men are gonna institute Sharia law.

118
00:07:46,816 --> 00:07:49,589
这婊子养的就在那看好戏
And that son of a bitch himself is gonna enjoy the show.

119
00:07:49,589 --> 00:07:51,550
我们低着头 不要管
We just have to keep our heads down and get through this

120
00:07:51,554 --> 00:07:53,476
今晚上就能出去了
so we can get out tonight.

121
00:08:03,960 --> 00:08:05,296
不 不 别让他们带走我
No. No, don't let them take me!

122
00:08:05,301 --> 00:08:05,925
不
No!

123
00:08:30,292 --> 00:08:32,626
-对不起  -不要
- Sorry. - No!

124
00:08:39,700 --> 00:08:41,300
拉马尔
Ramal!

125
00:08:45,270 --> 00:08:48,500
让开 放他走
Get back. Just let him go.

126
00:08:49,250 --> 00:08:50,310
拉马尔
Ramal!

127
00:08:52,240 --> 00:08:53,210
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?

128
00:08:53,210 --> 00:08:54,180
-你别管  -不行
- Stay out of this.  - No.

129
00:08:54,180 --> 00:08:55,540
今天我们就要逃出去
The escape is tonight.

130
00:08:55,580 --> 00:08:58,180
如果你想出去 我和他都必不可少
If you want to get out, you need me and you need him.

131
00:08:58,180 --> 00:08:59,610
说重点
Get to the point.

132
00:09:01,080 --> 00:09:02,550
放了他 拉马尔
Let him go, Ramal.

133
00:09:09,290 --> 00:09:10,500
你不放的话我来
Then I'll do it.

134
00:09:10,770 --> 00:09:12,150
不准碰他
Do not touch him.

135
00:09:12,150 --> 00:09:13,600
退后 狗娘养的
Get back, dog!

136
00:09:17,620 --> 00:09:21,440
监狱里不准杀人 明白吗
There will be no killing in this prison.... Understand?

137
00:09:31,520 --> 00:09:33,320
之前迈克尔想联系她
He's tried to contact her before.

138
00:09:33,350 --> 00:09:36,110
区别是这次他做到了
Only difference is he succeeded this time.

139
00:09:36,380 --> 00:09:39,290
非常聪明... 借助这个小孩来传达
It's smart... going through the boy.

140
00:09:41,010 --> 00:09:42,530
问个问题
Ask a question?

141
00:09:45,700 --> 00:09:47,700
为什么我们不直接干掉这个女的
Why are we pulling our punches with this woman?

142
00:09:50,160 --> 00:09:51,670
我前几天被派去她家里找她
I got sent to her house a couple of days ago,

143
00:09:51,670 --> 00:09:53,640
伤了她家人 不过我正要杀她的时候
started spilling blood, but I'm just supposed to stop

144
00:09:53,640 --> 00:09:55,510
就要我收手
before I start spilling hers.

145
00:09:57,440 --> 00:09:58,440
这什么情况
How's that work?

146
00:09:58,640 --> 00:10:00,800
你要习惯波塞冬的游戏规则
You'll get used to Poseidon's game.

147
00:10:02,210 --> 00:10:03,810
就像国际象棋
It's all chess.

148
00:10:04,850 --> 00:10:06,450
一环扣一环
It's a performance.

149
00:10:10,060 --> 00:10:13,460
是为了让奥提斯和她联络而设的戏码
A performance designed to make Outis reach out to her.

150
00:10:13,910 --> 00:10:15,860
现在我们只需要静观其变
Now all we got to do is listen in,

151
00:10:15,920 --> 00:10:18,000
搞清楚他的计划
find out what his plans are.

152
00:10:19,200 --> 00:10:20,630
而且她还不知情
And she doesn't know it.

153
00:10:20,630 --> 00:10:23,370
她的作用就是引领我们找到迈克尔
She's the one that's going to lead us to him.

154
00:10:24,400 --> 00:10:25,770
他们说我早上就可以下床走路了
They said I can go in the morning.

155
00:10:25,780 --> 00:10:28,170
你的股动脉被切断了
Your femoral artery was severed.

156
00:10:28,170 --> 00:10:31,240
这可不是你想走就能走的
That's not something you usually just get up and walk away from.

157
00:10:31,240 --> 00:10:33,480
真的 他们说我可以下床了
Hey, they gave me the okay.

158
00:10:33,510 --> 00:10:35,310
他们可是这方面的专家 你不是哦
They're the doctors on this one, not you.

159
00:10:35,310 --> 00:10:38,590
我在这快要疯了 我要出去
And I'm going full mental in here, so I'm gonna go.

160
00:10:38,650 --> 00:10:40,210
好吧 这样如何
Okay. How about this?

161
00:10:40,210 --> 00:10:42,180
你出院的时候
When you are discharged,

162
00:10:42,550 --> 00:10:45,150
我们直接去你父母湖边的那座房子
why don't we go up to your parents' lake house?

163
00:10:45,290 --> 00:10:47,150
我带着迈克来接你 然后就可以走了
I'll just pick you up with Mike and we'll go.

164
00:10:47,850 --> 00:10:48,800
嗯
Mmm.

165
00:10:49,650 --> 00:10:51,520
你不想继续留在家里了 对吧
You don't want to be in the house, do you?

166
00:10:53,110 --> 00:10:54,220
有人闯进我家
Somebody comes into your house

167
00:10:54,220 --> 00:10:56,510
射伤了我丈夫 而且他们还在逍遥法外
and shoots up your husband and they're still out there.

168
00:10:57,090 --> 00:10:58,430
我当然不想呆家里
No.

169
00:11:00,130 --> 00:11:01,050
你笑什么
What?

170
00:11:01,050 --> 00:11:02,760
你下决心的时候
No, it's just something you do with your nose

171
00:11:02,800 --> 00:11:04,180
你的鼻子好有趣
when you're determined.

172
00:11:04,180 --> 00:11:05,750
-我的鼻子吗  -你的鼻子很微妙的
- With my nose? - It's subtle.

173
00:11:05,750 --> 00:11:07,500
-我是说 你的鼻子辨识度很强  -那挺好的
- I mean, it's really subtle. - Better be.

174
00:11:08,540 --> 00:11:10,570
脸真精致
The face is amazing.

175
00:11:11,680 --> 00:11:12,870
我意思是
I mean,

176
00:11:13,000 --> 00:11:16,540
你的面庞真是极致的细腻
the tiniest detail, less than a millimeter,

177
00:11:16,680 --> 00:11:18,410
能够分辨出所有东西
differentiates everything.

178
00:11:19,000 --> 00:11:21,510
同样的情感显示在别人脸上可能会...
An emotion on one person can be...

179
00:11:22,350 --> 00:11:24,000
很困惑
so troubled

180
00:11:25,230 --> 00:11:26,610
但在你的面容里
and on another...

181
00:11:28,780 --> 00:11:30,190
美极了
so beautiful.

182
00:11:31,090 --> 00:11:33,690
你不打算走了吗 内斯先生
You're not trying to get somewhere, are you, Mr. Ness?

183
00:11:34,290 --> 00:11:35,730
不 实际上
Yes, actually,

184
00:11:36,050 --> 00:11:37,260
我要走
I am.

185
00:11:53,510 --> 00:11:55,000
你好啊 亲爱的
Hello there.

186
00:11:56,350 --> 00:11:58,310
萨拉 我以友好的身份而来
I come as a compatriot, Sara.

187
00:11:58,910 --> 00:12:00,420
你走开 要不然我就要叫了
Get out of my way or I'll scream.

188
00:12:00,420 --> 00:12:01,700
千万别
Last thing I want.

189
00:12:09,720 --> 00:12:11,290
希望你知道
For your information,

190
00:12:11,290 --> 00:12:13,260
我清楚坎尼尔·奥提斯的事了
I know about Kaniel Outis.

191
00:12:17,830 --> 00:12:19,270
告诉我你都知道什么
Tell me what you know.

192
00:12:19,710 --> 00:12:21,920
我从福克斯河监狱出来的时候
The day I hit the bricks from Fox River,

193
00:12:21,930 --> 00:12:23,530
有个叫做奥提斯的人
someone named Outis,

194
00:12:23,530 --> 00:12:25,300
出自于一副善心
out of the goodness of their soul,

195
00:12:25,330 --> 00:12:28,780
主动为我支付了更换假肢的经费
unsolicited, pays for this modern prosthesis.

196
00:12:30,070 --> 00:12:31,430
这是啥
What's that?

197
00:12:31,470 --> 00:12:33,660
这可是一百万美金
A million bucks?

198
00:12:33,670 --> 00:12:35,740
别人可能连一分都不想给我这种可怜的人
Why would anyone come out of a pocket for a wretch like me,

199
00:12:35,740 --> 00:12:37,740
何况这是一百万美金呐
a penny, much less a million bucks?

200
00:12:38,680 --> 00:12:41,600
如果你来寻求这个答案 我真不知道
Yeah, if you're coming to me for answers, I don't have any.

201
00:12:41,600 --> 00:12:44,380
好吧 我找过答案 萨拉医生
Oh, I went looking for answers, Doc Sara.

202
00:12:44,640 --> 00:12:46,920
我在网上查了奥提斯这个名字
I looked up Outis on the Interwebs.

203
00:12:46,920 --> 00:12:49,290
但是冒出来了你前任老公的脸
Whose face comes up but your dead ex-husband's,

204
00:12:49,320 --> 00:12:50,910
貌似他还活着
looking very much alive.

205
00:12:50,910 --> 00:12:52,820
起死回生啊
Lazarus arisen from the dead.

206
00:12:53,740 --> 00:12:55,560
他和我们在下一盘很大的棋 对吧
He's drawing us into something, isn't he?

207
00:12:56,670 --> 00:12:58,730
他想得到什么 是吗
He wants something, doesn't he?

208
00:13:00,000 --> 00:13:02,150
你再敢靠近我或是我的家人 我就杀了你
Come near me or my family again, I will kill you.

209
00:13:02,150 --> 00:13:04,370
萨拉 你最好让我协助你
Better to have me on your side, Sara.

210
00:13:04,400 --> 00:13:06,600
我们能一起找到答案
We can figure this out together.

211
00:13:15,520 --> 00:13:18,390
我们都听到了墙外的战火之声
We have all heard the war outside.

212
00:13:18,850 --> 00:13:22,280
但只要我们还在监狱里面
But even if it is just within these walls,

213
00:13:22,290 --> 00:13:25,900
就要遵守这里的律法
the law of the land is still in place.

214
00:13:25,900 --> 00:13:30,390
真主的旨意取代了这片腐败土地的律法
The law of God supersedes the law of this corrupt land.

215
00:13:30,390 --> 00:13:33,960
我们可不能从文明人变回畜生
We will not be reduced to animals.

216
00:13:36,790 --> 00:13:38,930
真不敢相信你还信任他
Amazing you still trust him.

217
00:13:38,930 --> 00:13:41,440
他只是利用你逃出去 然后就会把你一脚踹开
He will use you for the escape and he will leave you.

218
00:13:41,940 --> 00:13:43,640
没有人越狱
No one's escaping.

219
00:13:44,580 --> 00:13:45,940
你谁啊
Who are you?

220
00:13:45,980 --> 00:13:47,540
我是这所监狱里
A man who knows your friend there

221
00:13:47,540 --> 00:13:49,010
最了解你朋友的那个人
more than anyone in this prison.

222
00:13:49,650 --> 00:13:51,550
我和他单独在一起很多年
I was in solitary with him for years.

223
00:13:51,550 --> 00:13:52,250
我也一样
Yeah, so was I.

224
00:13:52,280 --> 00:13:54,050
你不是住在他对面的牢房
But not in the cell across from him.

225
00:13:54,450 --> 00:13:57,120
他告诉我越狱的事情了
He told me about the escape.

226
00:13:57,880 --> 00:13:59,510
-我们必须联手  -不行
- We have to work together. - No.

227
00:13:59,740 --> 00:14:01,730
他想说服我和他一起
Tried to convince me to go with him,

228
00:14:01,930 --> 00:14:03,690
就我们两个
just the two of us.

229
00:14:04,610 --> 00:14:05,930
但我拒绝了他
But I told him no.

230
00:14:06,210 --> 00:14:08,000
我不会离开我兄弟的
I would not leave my brother.

231
00:14:08,030 --> 00:14:09,830
我心中有所信仰
That is the Army in me,

232
00:14:10,140 --> 00:14:12,040
我是基督徒
the Christian in me.

233
00:14:12,240 --> 00:14:13,740
他是个机会主义者
He is an opportunist.

234
00:14:13,760 --> 00:14:16,210
不管是谁 只要有利用价值的他都会用
He will use whoever he needs.

235
00:14:16,310 --> 00:14:18,780
我知道他告诉过你越狱计划 肯定说过
He has told you something about the escape. I know he has.

236
00:14:18,780 --> 00:14:20,580
你和他在一个牢房里
You were in the cell with him. You.

237
00:14:20,610 --> 00:14:23,250
在他把那个大恶魔放出去之前
You tell me, so I can help you,

238
00:14:23,630 --> 00:14:27,280
只要告诉我计划 我就能帮你
before he uses you to get that devil out

239
00:14:27,520 --> 00:14:30,080
要不然就只能留在这等死了
and we are all left here to die.

240
00:14:44,900 --> 00:14:47,300
我们需要护照 奥马尔 你能帮我们吗
We need passports, Omar. You think you can help us?

241
00:14:47,300 --> 00:14:49,630
等下 我们能信任这家伙吗
Hold on. We're gonna trust this guy?

242
00:14:49,810 --> 00:14:52,200
一开始就是他就把我的护照给搞走的
He's the one who stole my passport in the first place.

243
00:14:52,250 --> 00:14:54,160
兄弟 那次交易很公平的
It was honest bargaining, friend.

244
00:14:54,160 --> 00:14:55,930
我没有拿走任何东西 另外
I took nothing. Besides,

245
00:14:55,930 --> 00:14:58,270
你的护照早就不见了
your passport is long gone,

246
00:14:58,300 --> 00:15:00,870
远在海外 我敢打赌
somewhere far overseas by now, I bet.

247
00:15:00,900 --> 00:15:04,470
如果你想要的话 我能给你伪造一个
If you want, um, I can have the forgers make you another.

248
00:15:04,510 --> 00:15:07,040
从你这儿搞一个假护照吗
My own fake passport coming from you?

249
00:15:07,080 --> 00:15:09,190
你还有其他选择吗
You have another option?

250
00:15:10,650 --> 00:15:12,580
快点 我就要离开这里了
Quick. I'm leaving the city.

251
00:15:12,720 --> 00:15:15,150
所有地方都不安全
Nowhere is safe anymore.

252
00:15:15,420 --> 00:15:17,520
我要两个护照 一个是我的
I need two passports. One for me,

253
00:15:17,650 --> 00:15:20,220
另一个给我弟弟 迈克尔·斯科菲尔德
one for my brother, Michael Scofield.

254
00:15:23,460 --> 00:15:25,760
每个护照1000美元定金
$1,000 U.S. Each, deposit.

255
00:15:26,021 --> 00:15:28,480
等你拿货时 再付1000美金
$1,000 U.S. When you pick them up.

256
00:15:30,058 --> 00:15:30,770
C
C?

257
00:15:33,490 --> 00:15:35,454
如果你敢耍我 我会杀了你
You screw with me and I'll kill you.

258
00:15:35,781 --> 00:15:37,134
如果我耍你
I screw you,

259
00:15:37,149 --> 00:15:39,340
我不会来这里见你
I won't be around for you to kill me.

260
00:15:40,218 --> 00:15:41,636
今晚11点 希巴
eleven tonight, Sheba.

261
00:15:41,650 --> 00:15:42,989
护照会准备好的
Passports will be ready.

262
00:15:45,156 --> 00:15:47,141
那就是说我们必须分开行动
That means we're gonna have to split up.

263
00:15:47,150 --> 00:15:48,290
你们俩去拿护照
You two get the passports,

264
00:15:48,312 --> 00:15:50,480
我和我们的这位朋友去发电厂
and I'll go with our friend here to the power plant

265
00:15:50,480 --> 00:15:51,687
关掉所有电源
and kill the lights.

266
00:15:53,280 --> 00:15:54,858
救迈克尔出来
And we get Michael out.

267
00:15:56,727 --> 00:15:58,778
美国国务院的一位发言人宣传
A U.S. State Department spokesperson said

268
00:15:58,778 --> 00:15:59,709
也门的首都
the capital of Yemen

269
00:15:59,709 --> 00:16:01,549
几近瓦解
grows ever closer to collapse

270
00:16:01,549 --> 00:16:03,025
萨那早迟会落入伊斯兰国激进分子的手中
and it's only a matter of time

271
00:16:03,025 --> 00:16:05,970
只是时间问题
until Sana'a's fallen to the hands of ISIL radicals,

272
00:16:05,978 --> 00:16:09,270
最快明天就会全面沦陷
with the total collapse coming as soon as tomorrow.

273
00:16:13,069 --> 00:16:14,160
嗨
Hey.

274
00:16:15,898 --> 00:16:16,923
选一款智能手机吗
Looking for a smartphone?

275
00:16:16,930 --> 00:16:18,710
嗯 你...
Yeah. You, um...

276
00:16:18,821 --> 00:16:21,360
你这里也修手机 对吗
you fix phones, too, right?

277
00:16:21,381 --> 00:16:22,280
没错
Yeah.

278
00:16:22,320 --> 00:16:25,163
我感觉我的手机被人黑了
I think somebody hacked my cell.

279
00:16:30,610 --> 00:16:31,338
哇哦
Whoa.

280
00:16:32,363 --> 00:16:34,960
能找出是谁干的吗
Is there any chance you can help me figure out who?

281
00:16:53,178 --> 00:16:54,240
那个基督徒说
That Christian guy said

282
00:16:54,254 --> 00:16:56,887
你告诉他 你只会带他走 不管其他人
you told him you'd just take him. No one else.

283
00:16:56,901 --> 00:16:59,461
他是个骗子 你不会想跟他有任何关系的
He's a liar. You don't want anything to do with him.

284
00:16:59,460 --> 00:17:02,596
我不知道 基督徒 军人 似乎都比我优先
I don't know. Christian, Army, seems pretty up front to me.

285
00:17:02,603 --> 00:17:04,130
他有告诉你 他和他的兄弟
Did he happen to tell you about some of the arrests

286
00:17:04,138 --> 00:17:06,203
为什么会在他们的安检点被捕吗
he and his brother made at their security checkpoint?

287
00:17:06,210 --> 00:17:07,723
没有 他只说了你
No, focused on you.

288
00:17:07,738 --> 00:17:09,876
他们的嗜好是女人
They had a specialty: women.

289
00:17:09,883 --> 00:17:11,810
分尸后的尸体遍布也门
Body parts strewn around Yemen.

290
00:17:11,818 --> 00:17:13,389
那就是他们被关在这里的原因
That's why they're here.

291
00:17:13,396 --> 00:17:15,003
戴着十字架是一回事
Wearing a cross is one thing.

292
00:17:15,010 --> 00:17:17,556
-遵循基督教的生活又是另一回事  -好了 好吧 的确
- Living by it is another. - All right, okay, sure.

293
00:17:17,563 --> 00:17:19,192
只要你保证不会骗我
Just promise me I can trust you,

294
00:17:19,192 --> 00:17:20,910
我们今晚仍会行动
that we're still doing this tonight.

295
00:17:22,785 --> 00:17:23,860
这么多年来
All these years

296
00:17:23,869 --> 00:17:25,214
我们一直合作
we've been working together,

297
00:17:25,221 --> 00:17:26,923
你可以相信我
you've been able to trust me the whole time.

298
00:17:26,930 --> 00:17:28,887
过去的四年一直被困在洞里 坐在黑暗中
Last four years in the hole, sitting in the dark,

299
00:17:28,887 --> 00:17:30,880
我甚至听不到声音 我不知道
I couldn't even hear a voice. I don't know.

300
00:17:31,134 --> 00:17:32,407
也许事情已经变了 又或者...
Maybe something's changed or...

301
00:17:32,407 --> 00:17:34,058
什么都没变
Nothing's changed.

302
00:17:35,563 --> 00:17:37,738
波塞冬把我们塞进来是为了救拉马尔出去
Poseidon put us in here to get Ramal out,

303
00:17:37,738 --> 00:17:40,170
但之后他抛弃了我们 拉马尔是波塞冬的人
but then he abandoned us. Ramal is Poseidon's guy,

304
00:17:40,170 --> 00:17:42,712
不是我们的 他是头野兽
not ours. He's an animal.

305
00:17:42,887 --> 00:17:46,261
我建议你管好自己的嘴 这里有些人会说英文
I suggest you watch your mouth. Some of these guys speak English.

306
00:17:47,934 --> 00:17:49,541
为什么我们还要救他出去
Why are we still getting him out?

307
00:17:49,549 --> 00:17:52,436
我们告诉他 我们会救他出去 和真的救他出去不是一码事
We're telling him we're getting him out. There's a difference.

308
00:17:52,698 --> 00:17:53,723
我们必须装成是
We got to act like we're

309
00:17:53,745 --> 00:17:55,047
站在他那边的 直到我们不需要再假装
on his side until the moment we're not.

310
00:17:55,054 --> 00:17:56,829
但如果你只是假装站在我这边
But what if you're acting like you're on my side

311
00:17:56,829 --> 00:17:57,614
直到你不需要假装呢
till the moment you're not?

312
00:17:57,621 --> 00:17:58,996
你患妄想症了吗
You are getting paranoid.

313
00:17:58,996 --> 00:18:01,381
没错 被困了四年确实会这样
Yeah, well, four years in the box is gonna do that to you.

314
00:18:01,389 --> 00:18:02,680
我不会丢下你的
I'm not leaving you behind.

315
00:18:02,683 --> 00:18:04,887
-你是我最后的王牌  -我不知道
- You're my whip hand. - I don't know that.

316
00:18:04,890 --> 00:18:06,698
我怎么知道我是不是你的王牌呢
How do I know I'm your whip hand?

317
00:18:06,880 --> 00:18:10,145
-你以后会知道的  -我现在就要知道
-You'll understand later. -I want to understand now.

318
00:18:10,407 --> 00:18:11,229
好吗
Okay?

319
00:18:13,658 --> 00:18:15,396
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me.

320
00:18:15,949 --> 00:18:18,370
现在回答我 我是认真的
Answers, now. I'm serious.

321
00:18:18,625 --> 00:18:19,425
好吧
Okay.

322
00:18:20,443 --> 00:18:22,100
我说过了不要碰我
I said don't touch me!

323
00:18:22,887 --> 00:18:24,400
好吧
Okay. Mm.

324
00:18:24,443 --> 00:18:26,814
好吧 这很公平
Mm. Okay, that's fair.

325
00:18:30,100 --> 00:18:32,400
你想再被关进去 是吗
You want the hole again, huh?

326
00:18:32,414 --> 00:18:33,978
不 我们没事
No, we're good.

327
00:18:35,810 --> 00:18:36,705
不
No.

328
00:18:36,727 --> 00:18:37,789
我们很好
We're good.

329
00:18:38,458 --> 00:18:39,956
我们一点也不好
We're far from good.

330
00:18:53,040 --> 00:18:55,549
到了明天 我们就不需要担心他了
By tomorrow, we won't have to worry about him.

331
00:19:07,505 --> 00:19:08,683
把你的头低下
Keep your head down.

332
00:19:08,690 --> 00:19:10,930
不要和任何人有眼神接触
Don't make eye contact with anybody.

333
00:19:10,930 --> 00:19:13,287
到处都是伊斯兰国的支持者
A lot of ISIL sympathizers everywhere.

334
00:19:13,287 --> 00:19:15,832
我们拿到护照后就马上离开这里
We get our passports, we're out of here.

335
00:19:15,840 --> 00:19:17,003
明白了吗
Understand?

336
00:19:34,363 --> 00:19:35,716
打算离开吗
Planning on leaving?

337
00:19:36,210 --> 00:19:38,763
正好在光荣革命开始的时候
Right when the glorious revolution is beginning.

338
00:19:38,770 --> 00:19:41,549
我不是来这探讨政治的 我们只要护照
I'm not here for political discussion, just passports.

339
00:19:45,720 --> 00:19:47,163
先付钱
Money first.

340
00:19:48,298 --> 00:19:49,730
先给护照
Passports first.

341
00:20:01,752 --> 00:20:02,690
护照是空白的
They're empty.

342
00:20:04,940 --> 00:20:05,890
希巴
Sheba!

343
00:20:26,930 --> 00:20:29,709
很抱歉打了你 我可以解释
I'm sorry I hit you. I can explain

344
00:20:29,709 --> 00:20:30,814
你能解释为什么
Can you explain why

345
00:20:30,829 --> 00:20:32,632
任由那个男人杀我吗
you were going to let that man kill me?

346
00:20:32,640 --> 00:20:34,370
我不会让他杀你的
I wouldn't have let him kill you.

347
00:20:34,385 --> 00:20:37,447
你看起来和伊斯兰国的头是一伙的 朋友
You sure seem to be chums with the head of ISIL, friend.

348
00:20:37,454 --> 00:20:40,334
原来你也会参与这些谈话 贾
Didn't know you participated in these conversations, Ja.

349
00:20:40,334 --> 00:20:42,160
只有当事情有趣时
Only when they're interesting.

350
00:20:42,589 --> 00:20:44,145
而它们通常很无聊
And they're usually not.

351
00:20:45,141 --> 00:20:46,676
不管你们信不信
There are people in my government,

352
00:20:46,670 --> 00:20:48,280
美国政府里有人想要那个男人出去
believe it or not, who want that man out

353
00:20:48,280 --> 00:20:51,592
为了他们自己在这里的复杂外交政策
for their own convoluted foreign policy over here.

354
00:20:52,090 --> 00:20:54,000
那就是派我和威普来这里的工作
That's the job Whip and I were sent here to do.

355
00:20:54,029 --> 00:20:55,265
但是出于某些原因
But for some reason,

356
00:20:55,272 --> 00:20:56,700
我们被背叛了
we were betrayed.

357
00:20:57,185 --> 00:20:59,500
那就意味着我们不用带拉马尔出去了
Which means we're getting out without Ramal.

358
00:20:59,956 --> 00:21:02,341
而你们每一个人都对这个计划至关重要
And every one of you is crucial to that plan.

359
00:21:02,341 --> 00:21:03,178
怎么做
How?

360
00:21:03,340 --> 00:21:05,549
你所有的逃跑计划都已经准备好了
Your whole escape's already wired.

361
00:21:05,992 --> 00:21:07,578
灯灭之后 你们就越狱了
Lights out, you're over the wall.

362
00:21:08,436 --> 00:21:10,792
你还需要我这个韩国瘾君子做什么
What do you need a Korean junkie like me for?

363
00:21:10,814 --> 00:21:12,778
你的意思是韩国天才
Korean genius, you mean.

364
00:21:13,330 --> 00:21:15,527
翻出那座墙只是开始
Getting over that wall is just the start.

365
00:21:16,036 --> 00:21:17,570
一旦我们离开监狱
Once that happens,

366
00:21:17,578 --> 00:21:19,410
有些事情只有你能做
there are things only you can do.

367
00:21:19,440 --> 00:21:22,370
回到刚刚的问题 你打了我
Back on point: you hit me.

368
00:21:22,370 --> 00:21:25,510
你想要我证明我和你是一边的 而不是拉马尔
You wanted proof that I sided with you and not Ramal.

369
00:21:25,520 --> 00:21:27,010
打裂我的嘴唇能证明什么
And splitting my lip does that how?

370
00:21:27,010 --> 00:21:30,610
狗娘养的坎尼尔·奥提斯还在耍把戏 对吗
Son of a bitch Kaniel Outis keeps playing, doesn't he?

371
00:21:40,130 --> 00:21:41,527
我的表在哪
Where is my watch?

372
00:21:41,832 --> 00:21:43,185
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.

373
00:21:43,192 --> 00:21:44,727
哈 你不知道
Hmm. You don't?

374
00:21:45,803 --> 00:21:49,440
等我找到我的表后 我会把你砍成两半 明白了吗
I'm going to break you in half when I find that watch, you know?

375
00:21:54,240 --> 00:21:55,352
清查这里
Toss the cell.

376
00:22:22,741 --> 00:22:24,087
没在这里
It's not here.

377
00:22:28,910 --> 00:22:31,214
整个监狱进入一级防范禁闭
Order a lockdown of the whole prison.

378
00:22:31,229 --> 00:22:33,032
所有人回到各自的监室
No one gets out of their cells

379
00:22:33,040 --> 00:22:34,780
直到我的手表被找到
until that watch is found!

380
00:22:47,221 --> 00:22:50,327
我告诉你了 拉马尔哪也去不了 只有我们能离开
I told you, Ramal's not going anywhere. Only we are.

381
00:22:50,858 --> 00:22:53,210
我们和其他人一样被关起来了
We're gonna be locked in our box just like the rest of them,

382
00:22:53,216 --> 00:22:54,860
但只有我们这间牢房能逃出去
only our box has a way out.

383
00:22:54,868 --> 00:22:57,344
等两小时后灯都灭了
And in two hours when those lights go black,

384
00:22:57,472 --> 00:23:00,186
我们会像幽灵般从这里逃之夭夭
we're gonna disappear from this place like ghosts.

385
00:23:01,344 --> 00:23:02,832
好吧 我信
Yeah, all right.

386
00:23:26,704 --> 00:23:27,978
希巴
Sheba!

387
00:23:29,706 --> 00:23:31,850
和你一起的人是什么来头
Who are these men you work with?

388
00:23:36,080 --> 00:23:37,810
他们配不上你
They're beneath you.

389
00:23:37,813 --> 00:23:39,552
你才配不上我
You're beneath me.

390
00:23:44,997 --> 00:23:47,642
我不忍心伤害你
It pains me to hurt you,

391
00:23:47,786 --> 00:23:52,085
但好女人都就应该低声下气
but a good woman is a humble woman.

392
00:23:53,056 --> 00:23:54,762
记住这一点
Remember that.

393
00:23:56,485 --> 00:23:58,053
那些人是谁
Who are these men?

394
00:23:58,805 --> 00:24:00,229
跟你无关
Doesn't matter.

395
00:24:00,464 --> 00:24:01,861
他们要离境了
They're leaving.

396
00:24:02,741 --> 00:24:04,960
我不是坏人
I am not the bad guy here.

397
00:24:05,080 --> 00:24:07,690
你我有过旧情
You and I have a history.

398
00:24:07,840 --> 00:24:08,590
你小学
How I doted

399
00:24:08,590 --> 00:24:12,842
我就爱着你 我等啊等
on you in grade school, how I waited and I waited.

400
00:24:12,986 --> 00:24:15,125
你可不是等我
You did not wait.

401
00:24:15,130 --> 00:24:17,392
你是要强奸我
You tried to rape me!

402
00:24:21,830 --> 00:24:22,752
请
Please.

403
00:24:25,312 --> 00:24:28,645
请你 请你解开我
Please. Please untie me...

404
00:24:29,712 --> 00:24:32,208
我好挖出你剩下那只眼
so I can take your other eye.

405
00:24:45,130 --> 00:24:46,565
下午好
Afternoon.

406
00:24:47,722 --> 00:24:52,112
我在找部手机 一个女人从我这偷走的
I'm looking for a cell phone that a woman stole from me.

407
00:24:53,088 --> 00:24:54,533
她长这样
She looks like this?

408
00:24:57,640 --> 00:24:59,637
抱歉 我帮不上忙
No, can't help you.

409
00:24:59,642 --> 00:25:02,810
不能...还是不想
Can't... or won't?

410
00:25:02,810 --> 00:25:05,493
抱歉 店里有规定 没办法
Sorry. Store policy, that's all.

411
00:25:13,786 --> 00:25:16,210
你要干嘛
Hey, what are you doing?

412
00:25:17,034 --> 00:25:18,416
就...
Just...

413
00:25:18,549 --> 00:25:20,112
再问一遍
Let's go again.

414
00:25:21,482 --> 00:25:22,938
见过这人吗
Have you seen her?

415
00:25:24,282 --> 00:25:25,978
见过 见过
Yes. Yes!

416
00:25:26,250 --> 00:25:28,666
她来过 大概十分钟前
She was here, like, ten minutes ago.

417
00:25:28,666 --> 00:25:30,640
说有人黑了她手机 想查出来是谁
Said her phone was hacked and wanted to know who did it.

418
00:25:30,647 --> 00:25:32,814
她现在发现我们了 对吧
And now she knows, doesn't she?

419
00:25:37,520 --> 00:25:38,870
这是引我们上钩
She baited us.

420
00:25:57,440 --> 00:25:58,789
没路了
Dead end.

421
00:26:41,600 --> 00:26:42,869
有没有可能波塞冬会准许我们
Any chance Poseidon'll just

422
00:26:42,874 --> 00:26:45,472
-杀了她  -有这个可能
- let us kill her? - It might come to that.

423
00:27:11,210 --> 00:27:13,253
等逃出去了 你去哪
We get out, where are you going?

424
00:27:14,020 --> 00:27:15,477
躺在我的沙发上
Back to my couch.

425
00:27:16,064 --> 00:27:17,829
我的沙发在首尔
My couch in Seoul.

426
00:27:18,272 --> 00:27:20,096
那里是我的墙
Where the walls are mine,

427
00:27:20,533 --> 00:27:21,989
我的地板
the floors are mine,

428
00:27:23,925 --> 00:27:25,440
没人能进去抓我
no one can get to me.

429
00:27:25,904 --> 00:27:28,821
像原先那样与世隔绝
The world stays outside like it's supposed to.

430
00:27:30,778 --> 00:27:31,866
我要去卡尔加里
Calgary.

431
00:27:32,666 --> 00:27:33,861
加拿大吗
Canada?

432
00:27:34,597 --> 00:27:36,602
我要当个滑雪运动员
I'm going to be a ski jumper.

433
00:27:37,653 --> 00:27:40,202
你没见过雪吧
You've never seen snow, have you?

434
00:27:40,666 --> 00:27:42,026
没错
That's the point.

435
00:27:42,480 --> 00:27:45,466
我生活的这座城市的一切...
Everything in my life till now in this country...

436
00:27:45,493 --> 00:27:50,021
燥热 仇恨 永不下雪的天空
The heat, the hate, the skies that never snow.

437
00:27:50,405 --> 00:27:52,096
你在说这个世界
You talk about the world.

438
00:27:52,144 --> 00:27:54,165
我想去到世界的另一端
I want to be on the other side of it.

439
00:28:06,430 --> 00:28:07,616
爸 妈 你们好啊
Hey, Dad. Hey, Mom.

440
00:28:07,610 --> 00:28:08,885
嗨 儿子 莎拉
Hi, son. Yeah, Sara,

441
00:28:08,880 --> 00:28:12,256
-我来吧  -谢谢您
- let me, uh... - Thanks, sir.

442
00:28:12,250 --> 00:28:15,120
我接个电话 抱歉
Oh, give me one sec. Sorry.

443
00:28:16,944 --> 00:28:17,642
你好
Hello?

444
00:28:17,781 --> 00:28:20,821
你好 我是维修店的布莱恩 我激活了你的新手机
Hi. This is Brian at Jep's. I got this number

445
00:28:20,821 --> 00:28:22,590
得道了你的这个手机号
when I activated your new phone.

446
00:28:23,120 --> 00:28:24,181
你一直没回来取手机
You never came back.

447
00:28:24,192 --> 00:28:26,010
抱歉 我不会过来取了
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm going to.

448
00:28:26,016 --> 00:28:28,778
好吧 我想告诉你
Well, okay, I just want to let you know that

449
00:28:28,954 --> 00:28:31,045
我知道是谁黑了你的手机
I figured out who was hacking your phone.

450
00:28:31,253 --> 00:28:32,117
谁
Who?

451
00:28:32,440 --> 00:28:34,325
你...自己黑的
You... hacked your own phone.

452
00:28:34,336 --> 00:28:35,397
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

453
00:28:35,406 --> 00:28:38,598
你的指纹是你的密码 对吧
Your thumbprint is your password, right? Well,

454
00:28:38,600 --> 00:28:41,360
谁黑都需要你的指纹解锁 所以
whoever hacked your phone used your thumbprint, so,

455
00:28:41,370 --> 00:28:45,066
除非你少了根手指头 否则就是你自己
unless you're missing a thumb, that's you.

456
00:28:45,060 --> 00:28:46,234
我不知道你惹了什么麻烦
I don't know what you're messed up in,

457
00:28:46,234 --> 00:28:48,154
要是我就会小心...
but I'd watch your back...

458
00:28:50,752 --> 00:28:52,448
你住院的时候
When you were in the hospital,

459
00:28:52,448 --> 00:28:54,880
袭击我们的女人和她的搭档回来过
the woman who attacked us came back with her partner.

460
00:28:54,912 --> 00:28:55,616
什么
What?

461
00:28:55,632 --> 00:28:57,312
他们通过手机跟踪我
They tracked me down using my cell phone,

462
00:28:57,312 --> 00:28:59,658
所以我拿着手机去了维修店想搞清楚
so I brought it to Jep's to try and figure out

463
00:28:59,653 --> 00:29:01,840
-他们是谁派来的  -等等 莎拉 这事警察
- who they were working for. - Whoa, wait. Sara, this has police

464
00:29:01,845 --> 00:29:03,890
-都调查过了  -警察摆平不了这个
- written all over it. - Police haven't been able to do a thing.

465
00:29:03,893 --> 00:29:05,670
所以呢 你就去维修店
So, what? You went to Jep's Electronics

466
00:29:05,680 --> 00:29:07,872
耍老套的反间谍伎俩吗
in some hackneyed attempt at counter-espionage?

467
00:29:08,490 --> 00:29:10,448
抱歉 我很抱歉 只是...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just...

468
00:29:11,765 --> 00:29:13,621
我知道你束手无策
I get you don't know where to turn,

469
00:29:13,685 --> 00:29:14,954
可这事也关系到我
but I got a stake in this, too.

470
00:29:14,965 --> 00:29:17,536
你是我老婆 那是我儿子
Okay? This is my wife, my son.

471
00:29:19,178 --> 00:29:20,757
你想报复那些人吗
You want to get back at these guys?

472
00:29:20,778 --> 00:29:23,024
我们大学里有真能帮你的
The university. I mean, it has real resources,

473
00:29:23,029 --> 00:29:24,330
计算机科学系
their computer sciences department.

474
00:29:24,330 --> 00:29:26,350
手机没问题啦 就放维修店吧
The phone's done. It's gonna stay at Jep's.

475
00:29:27,125 --> 00:29:30,245
你的计划... 就是掩耳盗铃吗
So that's your plan... just bury your head in the sand?

476
00:29:32,538 --> 00:29:33,461
不是
No.

477
00:29:34,666 --> 00:29:35,877
不是 这些年我学到的
No, I've learned over the years

478
00:29:35,872 --> 00:29:37,829
正是那些你不会做的 谢谢了
that's exactly what you don't do. Thank you.

479
00:29:51,098 --> 00:29:52,490
哪位
Which one's this?

480
00:29:52,992 --> 00:29:55,013
你在厕所里搭讪的人
The one you accosted in a bathroom.

481
00:29:55,029 --> 00:29:57,525
那才不是搭讪 宝贝
Oh, that wasn't accostment, honey.

482
00:29:57,530 --> 00:29:59,301
我得到些情报
I've learned some things

483
00:30:00,272 --> 00:30:03,141
很显然关乎你我正在共同寻找的人
about who it is we're apparently both looking for?

484
00:30:03,973 --> 00:30:06,448
我想知道你是否愿为真相坚持到底
But I need to know that you're willing to go the distance.

485
00:30:06,570 --> 00:30:08,698
我就是为坚持而生 小烈女
I'm made of the distance, honeysuckle.

486
00:30:08,693 --> 00:30:10,600
我就是坚持的化身
I am the distance.

487
00:30:10,610 --> 00:30:13,061
好 你要替我和
Good. Because you're gonna have a conversation

488
00:30:13,090 --> 00:30:14,832
保罗·凯勒曼谈话
with Paul Kellerman for me.

489
00:30:15,104 --> 00:30:17,733
靠 是凯勒曼在背后搞鬼吗
Bull. Kellerman's behind this?

490
00:30:17,733 --> 00:30:19,376
你要尽可能拼凑所有的信息
And you are gonna get every shred of information

491
00:30:19,376 --> 00:30:21,626
搞清到底怎么回事
you can about what's really going on.

492
00:30:23,700 --> 00:30:25,210
十五分钟
15 minutes.

493
00:30:28,309 --> 00:30:30,928
你要知道我在这坐以待毙
I'm soiling myself here, just so you know.

494
00:30:37,312 --> 00:30:40,101
听着 我只想说一件事
Look, I'm just gonna say one thing, okay?

495
00:30:41,072 --> 00:30:42,688
我把你当兄弟
You're like a brother to me,

496
00:30:43,660 --> 00:30:45,477
当大哥
like an older brother.

497
00:30:45,904 --> 00:30:47,870
-我不太像哥哥  -确实
- I'm not much of a brother. - Sure.

498
00:30:47,870 --> 00:30:50,992
重点是在你招募我之前 我无依无靠
Point is that I had zero, nobody, till you recruited me.

499
00:30:51,973 --> 00:30:52,853
那时你帮我逃出
When you pulled me out of

500
00:30:52,853 --> 00:30:55,029
欧扎克的监狱 你很守信
that prison in the Ozarks, you had integrity.

501
00:30:58,725 --> 00:31:01,285
我知道我们在为中情局工作
I know we were doing CIA work, sure,

502
00:31:01,285 --> 00:31:02,940
救他们的人出来
you know, pulling their people out, but

503
00:31:03,445 --> 00:31:07,216
但这关乎你我二人 互相照应
it was about you and me, and having each other's back.

504
00:31:07,216 --> 00:31:09,738
就算在哥伦比亚越狱那时你叫
And it didn't matter if you were Ramon Cadena when we did

505
00:31:09,738 --> 00:31:13,274
雷蒙·卡德纳也没关系 或是阿萨...
the Colombian break, or, you know Asaf...

506
00:31:13,600 --> 00:31:14,784
叫什么来着
What was his name?

507
00:31:15,472 --> 00:31:17,029
不重要 那个埃及名
Whatever. The one in Egypt.

508
00:31:18,384 --> 00:31:19,642
你还是你
You were still you.

509
00:31:20,213 --> 00:31:22,261
这次也是一样
And it's the same with this one.

510
00:31:23,968 --> 00:31:26,677
我们视你为坎尼尔·奥提斯
You know, we trump you up as Kaniel Outis,

511
00:31:26,677 --> 00:31:28,549
头号恐怖分子
big international terrorist.

512
00:31:29,200 --> 00:31:30,613
就是个名字
It's just a name,

513
00:31:31,749 --> 00:31:34,458
只是个犯罪记录 为了把你关起来
it's just a rap sheet, it's a way to get you locked up.

514
00:31:36,016 --> 00:31:36,860
好吗
Right?

515
00:31:39,274 --> 00:31:41,957
可能我要求你的...
I guess what I'm asking you is...did...

516
00:31:42,768 --> 00:31:45,568
你被关禁闭的时候发生了什么事吗
did something happen to you while you were in solitary?

517
00:31:47,888 --> 00:31:49,701
你在那里的时候 思想上已经变成了
Did you become Kaniel Outis

518
00:31:49,701 --> 00:31:51,066
坎尼尔·奥提斯了吗
in there in your head?

519
00:31:53,573 --> 00:31:56,362
你现在真心希望救拉马尔出去吗
Do you now want Ramal out after all?

520
00:31:56,416 --> 00:31:59,670
我已经明确告诉过你 拉马尔不在越狱计划中
I already told you Ramal is ou of the picture.

521
00:31:59,679 --> 00:32:02,146
你是说过 但是有件小事儿...
Yeah, you said that, but one small thing...

522
00:32:02,140 --> 00:32:03,989
我们要穿过那个洞
We go up through that hole,

523
00:32:04,992 --> 00:32:06,926
然后绕开那个片区
and then we skirt above the block.

524
00:32:06,981 --> 00:32:10,005
正好会经过拉马尔的监室上方 不是吗
Goes right above Ramal's cell, doesn't it?

525
00:32:10,910 --> 00:32:12,869
只要敲掉点瓷砖
Knock out a couple tiles,

526
00:32:13,589 --> 00:32:15,434
他不就可以一起跑了吗
he joins the escape, doesn't he?

527
00:32:20,197 --> 00:32:21,376
那天打完架
What did you whisper to him

528
00:32:21,376 --> 00:32:22,944
你到底跟他耳语了什么
in that moment after the fight?

529
00:32:25,072 --> 00:32:26,928
你悄悄跟他说话了 说了些什么
You whispered something, what was it?

530
00:32:30,469 --> 00:32:32,080
还有九分钟
Nine minutes.

531
00:32:33,040 --> 00:32:34,250
你怎么知道的
How do you know?

532
00:32:34,725 --> 00:32:36,261
他晚饭的时候跟我说的
He told me at dinner.

533
00:32:36,666 --> 00:32:38,698
他说他会来找我们的
He said he would come for us.

534
00:32:39,056 --> 00:32:40,741
本来只有我一个人的
It's supposed to be only me,

535
00:32:42,800 --> 00:32:45,946
但我允许你们一起越狱
but you will all be coming.

536
00:32:47,090 --> 00:32:48,784
打开五号牢房
Open block five.

537
00:32:52,341 --> 00:32:53,504
全部出来
Everyone out.

538
00:32:53,509 --> 00:32:54,480
彻查监仓
Shakedown.

539
00:33:08,357 --> 00:33:09,392
找到了
Got it.

540
00:33:10,390 --> 00:33:13,408
找到了 穆斯塔法 在埃米尔的外套里
Found it, Mustapha. It was in the emir's coat here.

541
00:33:15,125 --> 00:33:17,493
你信了那个骗子 是不是
You trusted the liar, didn't you?

542
00:33:22,110 --> 00:33:24,469
现在 我们就只有祈祷灯赶紧关掉了
Now, we just pray they get the lights out.

543
00:33:26,464 --> 00:33:27,909
我们必须要加紧速度了
We got to hurry, man.

544
00:33:27,914 --> 00:33:29,109
我们只有不到十分钟时间
We got less than ten minutes

545
00:33:29,109 --> 00:33:30,378
断掉电源
to kill the power.

546
00:33:31,173 --> 00:33:32,420
不用担心
Don't worry.

547
00:33:32,431 --> 00:33:34,972
运气好的话 你朋友和我儿子
With luck, both your friend and my son

548
00:33:34,970 --> 00:33:37,162
在一个小时内都可以重获自由
will be free within the hour.

549
00:33:39,280 --> 00:33:41,477
好 断路器关掉了
Okay, breakers are down.

550
00:33:41,472 --> 00:33:43,520
现在只需要关掉冗余电能
Now, we just need to pull the redundancies.

551
00:33:43,520 --> 00:33:44,602
他们在大厅里
They're down the hall.

552
00:33:44,602 --> 00:33:46,890
我留在对付保安 你快去吧
I'll stay here and deal with security. Go.

553
00:33:49,072 --> 00:33:50,026
好吧
Okay.

554
00:33:50,496 --> 00:33:52,304
在哪 在哪呢
Come on, where are you?

555
00:33:56,608 --> 00:33:58,336
不是吧
Oh, come on.

556
00:33:59,738 --> 00:34:02,010
好吧 要是不知道该怎么办 就用老办法
Oh, when in doubt, go old school.

557
00:34:17,056 --> 00:34:18,390
该走了
Let's go.

558
00:34:22,100 --> 00:34:23,376
赶紧启动发电机
Get the generators up.

559
00:34:23,370 --> 00:34:24,928
把这些囚犯关回牢房
Get these inmates back inside!

560
00:34:24,922 --> 00:34:25,914
赶紧
Now!

561
00:34:34,309 --> 00:34:35,648
快跑 快跑
Let's go, let's go!

562
00:34:36,896 --> 00:34:38,950
武器 带上他们的武器
The weapons, get their weapons.

563
00:34:48,474 --> 00:34:50,234
他们不打算带上我们一起跑了
They are trying to escape without us.

564
00:34:50,234 --> 00:34:51,360
快去找他们
Get to their cell.

565
00:34:51,370 --> 00:34:53,194
六区监室 走啊
Block six. Come on!

566
00:35:01,648 --> 00:35:02,720
你听到了 兄弟
You heard them, brother.

567
00:35:02,768 --> 00:35:04,293
-六区牢房  -是的
- Block six. - Yes.

568
00:35:04,853 --> 00:35:06,090
贾 把你的手机给我
Ja, give me your phone.

569
00:35:06,090 --> 00:35:07,178
给你
Come on.

570
00:35:13,706 --> 00:35:14,880
装上手电
Mount flashlights.

571
00:35:14,880 --> 00:35:16,213
封锁每间牢房
Secure every room.

572
00:35:16,293 --> 00:35:17,760
不到万不得已 不要开枪
Shoot only if you have to.

573
00:35:17,765 --> 00:35:20,005
要是开枪了 确保击毙
And if you do, shoot to kill.

574
00:35:41,888 --> 00:35:43,130
这边
This way.

575
00:35:43,472 --> 00:35:45,856
这边去六区牢房更近 快点
A shortcut to block six, brother, come on!

576
00:35:46,048 --> 00:35:48,282
放开我 你这个变态
Get off me, you sick bastard!

577
00:35:48,282 --> 00:35:50,906
你不挣扎的话会简单点
It's easier if you don't struggle.

578
00:36:18,421 --> 00:36:20,554
你就这么对我吗
This is how you treat me?

579
00:36:20,778 --> 00:36:23,408
贱母狗 你准备受死吧
You're going to die now, dog.

580
00:36:40,746 --> 00:36:43,653
希巴 希巴 是我
Sheba, Sheba, it's me, it's me.

581
00:36:43,653 --> 00:36:44,778
你还好吗
Are you okay?

582
00:36:56,768 --> 00:36:57,800
林肯 快说
Linc, talk to me.

583
00:36:57,808 --> 00:37:00,288
快去集合点 那个汽车店
Get to the rendezvous, the auto shop.

584
00:37:00,288 --> 00:37:02,288
我们到不了了 希巴被伤得很严重
We ain't gonna make it. Sheba's busted up real bad.

585
00:37:02,288 --> 00:37:04,656
-怎么回事  -你先去集合点吧
- What happened? - Just get to the rendezvous.

586
00:37:04,656 --> 00:37:06,848
为了迈克一定要去
We got to be there for Michael, damn it!

587
00:37:10,112 --> 00:37:12,448
操 全仓戒严
Damn. Lockdown.

588
00:37:12,464 --> 00:37:14,053
屋顶上还有额外的守卫
Extra guards on the roof.

589
00:37:14,064 --> 00:37:16,144
重点是他们会不会离开
Question is whether they move on.

590
00:37:17,722 --> 00:37:19,621
快点 快点
Quickly! Hurry, hurry!

591
00:37:19,696 --> 00:37:21,445
这间 这间
It's here, this one!

592
00:37:23,818 --> 00:37:25,130
出事儿了
We got problems.

593
00:37:25,136 --> 00:37:27,792
-有人想进我们这间牢房  -有情况
- Guys are trying to get into the cell. - Problem.

594
00:37:27,792 --> 00:37:29,216
-什么情况  -有人来了
- What's wrong? - People coming.

595
00:37:29,210 --> 00:37:30,682
操 上面有守卫
Damn it, we got guards up here.

596
00:37:30,688 --> 00:37:32,069
想办法给我们争取点时间
Try and buy us some time.

597
00:37:32,453 --> 00:37:33,830
我来争取
I'm taking care of it.

598
00:37:36,453 --> 00:37:38,170
他们已经要跑了 快点啊
No, they're escaping, hurry!

599
00:37:43,178 --> 00:37:45,797
求你们了 别丢下我们不管
No, please! Don't leave us.

600
00:37:45,797 --> 00:37:46,954
我们是基督徒
Please, we are Christians,

601
00:37:46,960 --> 00:37:48,640
他们会杀了我们的 求你了
they will kill us! Please!

602
00:37:48,640 --> 00:37:50,218
上面还没处理完
No, we're still not clear up top.

603
00:37:50,210 --> 00:37:51,877
快确保他们上不来
Make sure they don't get up.

604
00:37:52,021 --> 00:37:52,949
快爬
Go!

605
00:37:53,509 --> 00:37:54,453
他们要上来了 贾
They're coming, Ja.

606
00:37:54,458 --> 00:37:56,290
-进展怎么样了  -不太好
- How we doing? - Not good.

607
00:37:56,378 --> 00:37:58,384
守卫反而更近了
Guards are even closer.

608
00:37:58,400 --> 00:37:59,728
把自己拉上去
Pull yourself up!

609
00:38:06,170 --> 00:38:07,776
救命啊 救我
Help, help!

610
00:38:09,413 --> 00:38:10,410
锡德
Sid!

611
00:38:14,261 --> 00:38:15,274
锡德
Sid!

612
00:38:18,666 --> 00:38:19,696
把我拉上去
Help me out!

613
00:38:19,690 --> 00:38:20,810
你先把他拉上来
Get him up here first.

614
00:38:20,810 --> 00:38:21,978
这样不行
That's not how this works.

615
00:38:21,970 --> 00:38:24,117
你先把我兄弟拉上去
You pull my brother up first.

616
00:38:24,117 --> 00:38:26,085
快点 拉马尔要来了
Hurry, Ramal is coming.

617
00:38:26,096 --> 00:38:28,458
把你的手给我 我发誓我会...
Lend me your hand. I swear I'm gonna...

618
00:38:28,453 --> 00:38:30,160
先把那小伙子拉上来
The kid comes up first!

619
00:38:32,512 --> 00:38:34,330
别动 别动
Step away, step away.

620
00:38:34,880 --> 00:38:36,688
-不  -穆扎 穆扎 看着我
- No! - Muza, Muza, look at me!

621
00:38:36,698 --> 00:38:38,629
穆扎 你别死
Muza! Muza!

622
00:38:38,620 --> 00:38:40,624
别死啊 睁开眼睛
No! No, look at me, brother.

623
00:38:40,714 --> 00:38:43,408
快跑 快跑 拉马尔来了
Go, go, go! It's Ramal.

624
00:38:43,962 --> 00:38:45,824
睁开眼睛啊
Look at me! Muza!

625
00:38:52,420 --> 00:38:55,034
要赶紧了 最多只有一分钟的时间离开这里
Hurry. We've got a minute tops to get out of here.

626
00:38:55,030 --> 00:38:55,712
快上去 追他
Get up there, after him.

627
00:38:55,712 --> 00:38:56,896
扔掉武器
Drop them!

628
00:38:57,541 --> 00:38:58,682
赶紧扔掉
Drop them!

629
00:39:00,522 --> 00:39:01,909
放下武器
Put it down!

630
00:39:07,765 --> 00:39:08,970
快点
Do it!

631
00:39:11,760 --> 00:39:14,442
-不  -放下 现在
- No! - Down, now!

632
00:39:15,653 --> 00:39:17,940
-板子跨越间隙  -毯子盖着电线
- Board spans the gap. - Blanket covers the wire.

633
00:39:17,952 --> 00:39:19,829
出来
Get out!

634
00:39:25,653 --> 00:39:27,509
你们跑到这间牢房里干什么
What are you doing in this cell?

635
00:39:30,261 --> 00:39:31,920
他们在屋顶上
They're on the roof!

636
00:39:43,349 --> 00:39:44,490
别开枪
Don't shoot!

637
00:40:42,837 --> 00:40:44,805
我这么信任你 坎尼尔·奥提斯
I trusted you, Kaniel Outis.

638
00:40:44,821 --> 00:40:46,130
你却骗了我
And you lied to me.

639
00:40:46,373 --> 00:40:50,106
我用上帝和伊斯兰国军队的名义起誓
By God and my armies of the caliphate,

640
00:40:50,101 --> 00:40:51,400
你死定了
you will die for it.

641
00:40:51,941 --> 00:40:53,630
说不定明天就死了
Maybe even tomorrow.

642
00:41:39,072 --> 00:41:40,032
萨拉...
Sara...

643
00:41:42,725 --> 00:41:44,965
我接下来说的话可能会把你推进火坑
I'm putting you in danger by saying this,

644
00:41:45,989 --> 00:41:48,341
但也许没什么关系 因为我马上要死了
but maybe it doesn't matter because I'll be dead,

645
00:41:49,424 --> 00:41:50,842
这样至少他们不会再去烦你
and they'll leave you alone.

646
00:41:54,069 --> 00:41:55,445
我爱你
But I love you.

647
00:41:57,952 --> 00:41:59,200
听到了吗 我爱你
You see, I loved you.

648
00:42:01,157 --> 00:42:03,029
我无时无刻不爱你
I never stopped loving you.

649
00:42:05,680 --> 00:42:09,189
这整个谎 都是为了你
This whole lie, it was for you.

650
00:42:10,922 --> 00:42:13,792
萨拉 如果我... 如果我真的死了
Sara, if I... if I do die,

651
00:42:15,445 --> 00:42:18,352
别让他们在墓碑上刻坎尼尔·奥提斯这个名字
don't let them put Kaniel Outis on the headstone

652
00:42:20,325 --> 00:42:22,420
因为这根本就是假的
because that's never what it was.

653
00:42:24,128 --> 00:42:26,314
能不能刻上我自己的名字
Make them put my real name,

654
00:42:27,573 --> 00:42:29,525
那个真正的我
the man I have always been.

655
00:42:34,458 --> 00:42:36,032
迈克尔·斯科菲尔德
Michael Scofield.

656
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:30,000
{\fn锐字工房光芒黑简1.0\fs20\move(300,10,10,10)\an7\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}电影淘淘
{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\move(300,10,10,10)\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}WWW.{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\1c&H0080FF&\b0\i1}DYTTBD.COM

657
00:00:30,000 --> 02:00:00,000
{\fn锐字工房光芒黑简1.0\fs20\pos(10,10)\an7\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}电影淘淘
{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\pos(10,10)\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}WWW.{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\1c&H0080FF&\b0\i1}DYTTBD.COM

658
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:15,000
{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&H6D04FB&\b0}更多电影美剧尽在（{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&HE6E600&\b0}电影淘淘 www.dyttbd.com{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&H6D04FB&\b0}）
