1
00:00:02,410 --> 00:00:03,620
你不用工作吗
Don't you have a job or something?

2
00:00:03,700 --> 00:00:04,890
要啊 我在一艘私人运营的船上打杂
Yeah, on a freelance cargo ship.

3
00:00:04,990 --> 00:00:06,690
我们去了香港 西班牙
We go to Hong Kong, Spain,

4
00:00:06,800 --> 00:00:08,760
布宜诺斯艾利斯 基本老板说哪就去哪
Buenos Aires, basically wherever the boss tells us.

5
00:00:08,840 --> 00:00:10,360
婊子养的糜烂货
Corrupt son of a bitch.

6
00:00:10,470 --> 00:00:12,280
我们唤醒了某些东西 有些人不想让我们
We've awoken something, something people are trying to

7
00:00:12,360 --> 00:00:13,330
知道迈克尔的事情
hide about Michael.

8
00:00:13,440 --> 00:00:14,870
这个什么波塞冬到底是谁?
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?

9
00:00:14,970 --> 00:00:16,240
是个变态
A psychopath.

10
00:00:16,340 --> 00:00:18,010
中情局里一个失意的
A frustrated policy wonk

11
00:00:18,110 --> 00:00:20,110
政策研究员 在中情局内部创立了一个
in the CIA who created a cell

12
00:00:20,210 --> 00:00:23,210
叫"21空洞"的组织
within the CIA called 21-Void.

13
00:00:23,310 --> 00:00:24,750
而他需要我
And they needed my help

14
00:00:24,850 --> 00:00:25,980
帮助被关押在世界各地
breaking out people in prison

15
00:00:26,080 --> 00:00:27,820
的囚犯越狱
all over the world.

16
00:00:27,850 --> 00:00:29,120
凯勒曼遇害之前
Before he was killed,

17
00:00:29,150 --> 00:00:30,850
正在调查21空洞的事情
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.

18
00:00:30,890 --> 00:00:32,120
我需要你调查系统内部
I need you to look into the possibility

19
00:00:32,160 --> 00:00:34,520
存在内鬼的可能性
that there was an insider involved.

20
00:00:34,560 --> 00:00:36,260
没想到你会在这时候打电话给我
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.

21
00:00:36,290 --> 00:00:37,560
我们得尽快见面
I think we need to meet soon.

22
00:00:37,590 --> 00:00:39,360
我在找那个叔叔去哪儿了
I was looking for where the man went.

23
00:00:39,400 --> 00:00:40,430
什么叔叔 宝贝儿?
What man, baby?

24
00:00:40,460 --> 00:00:41,700
给我这个的叔叔
The man that gave me this.

25
00:00:41,730 --> 00:00:42,860
迈克尔
Michael.

26
00:00:42,900 --> 00:00:45,130
你到底遇到什么麻烦了
What are you into?

27
00:00:45,170 --> 00:00:46,700
告诉我们你要去哪儿
Just tell us where you're headed.

28
00:00:46,740 --> 00:00:49,170
穿过沙漠三百英里外的费阿刻斯
300 miles across the desert, Phaeacia.

29
00:00:49,210 --> 00:00:51,140
一个自治区 没有ISIL
Autonomous zone. No ISIL.

30
00:00:51,170 --> 00:00:52,340
我可以带你们过去
I can lead you there.

31
00:00:52,380 --> 00:00:54,110
费阿刻斯 我们找到了!
Phaeacia, we found it!

32
00:01:07,260 --> 00:01:10,960
在城里的时候 我就告诉过你 你会死的
Back in the city, I told you you would die.

33
00:01:10,990 --> 00:01:12,030
迈克尔
Michael.

34
00:01:12,060 --> 00:01:13,860
他对我下了毒
He poisoned me.

35
00:01:37,650 --> 00:01:41,220
你画画越来越好 真是不可思议 迈克
It's incredible how good you've gotten at drawing, Mike.

36
00:01:41,260 --> 00:01:43,890
真的 这...
Really, that's...

37
00:01:43,930 --> 00:01:45,830
太好看了
that's so good.

38
00:01:45,860 --> 00:01:48,230
这是个希腊英雄
It's a Greek hero.

39
00:01:48,260 --> 00:01:49,860
他好像受伤了
He looks hurt.

40
00:01:49,900 --> 00:01:52,300
他们早晚都会受伤的
They all get hurt sooner or later.

41
00:01:52,340 --> 00:01:55,170
这才是古希腊英雄的伟大之处
That's what's great about Greek heroes,

42
00:01:55,200 --> 00:01:58,270
他们是真实的 而不是超人
they're real, not supermen.

43
00:01:58,310 --> 00:02:00,210
他们也会受伤
They get hurt.

44
00:02:00,240 --> 00:02:01,610
也会死
They can die.

45
00:02:10,920 --> 00:02:13,020
不好意思 哥们儿 最后一点儿就好
Hey, I'm sorry, buddy, last little bit.

46
00:02:13,060 --> 00:02:15,060
我得把伤口洗干净 知道吗
I got to keep it clean, you know?

47
00:02:15,090 --> 00:02:16,720
看上去好多了 不是吗
It's looking much better though, okay?

48
00:02:16,760 --> 00:02:18,760
你没问题的 坚持住 兄弟
You're doing good. You just hang in there, buddy.

49
00:02:19,560 --> 00:02:20,790
怎么样了
How we doing?

50
00:02:20,830 --> 00:02:22,460
有进展了
Got something.

51
00:02:22,500 --> 00:02:24,180
咱们那边的那位朋友有艘船
Our friend over there has a boat.

52
00:02:24,260 --> 00:02:26,400
他正要往希腊运趟走私货
He's making a smuggling run to Greece.

53
00:02:26,440 --> 00:02:29,370
他说他能带你弟弟去第一世界看医生
He says he can take your brother to a first world doctor.

54
00:02:29,410 --> 00:02:31,570
第一世界的人都认为他是肯尼尔·奥提斯
First world thinks he's Kaniel Outis.

55
00:02:31,610 --> 00:02:33,110
一见面他们就会逮捕他的
They'll arrest him on sight.

56
00:02:33,140 --> 00:02:34,580
所以呢
So?

57
00:02:34,610 --> 00:02:35,910
还能怎么办 看着他死吗
What's the alternative, let him die?

58
00:02:35,950 --> 00:02:37,280
你到底算是个什么哥哥啊
What kind of a brother are you?

59
00:02:39,880 --> 00:02:41,150
你再说一次这种话
You say something like that again,

60
00:02:41,180 --> 00:02:42,950
我发誓一定亲手杀了你
I swear to God, I'll kill you.

61
00:02:49,560 --> 00:02:51,660
也许还有第三个选择
There might be a third option.

62
00:03:00,370 --> 00:03:02,600
第一天回去上班感觉如何
So how was your first day back?

63
00:03:04,170 --> 00:03:06,610
必须承认 我从来没这么有成就感过
I have to say, it's never been so rewarding

64
00:03:06,640 --> 00:03:07,840
往一帮十八岁小屁孩的头脑里
to teach game theory to the tops

65
00:03:07,880 --> 00:03:09,280
灌输博弈论
of a bunch of 18-year-olds' heads

66
00:03:09,310 --> 00:03:10,910
尽管他们只是忙着互发色情短信
while they're busy sexting each other.

67
00:03:13,480 --> 00:03:14,880
不过
But...

68
00:03:14,920 --> 00:03:17,480
正常的日子离我们不远了
normalcy's threatening to come back,

69
00:03:17,520 --> 00:03:19,720
这必须庆祝一下
and I say cheers to that.

70
00:03:19,760 --> 00:03:21,060
值得庆祝
Cheers to that.

71
00:03:22,790 --> 00:03:24,390
来吧 咱们到外面坐坐
Come on, let's sit outside.

72
00:03:26,160 --> 00:03:27,800
我一会就过去
I'll be right there.

73
00:03:33,170 --> 00:03:34,440
喂?
Hello?

74
00:03:34,470 --> 00:03:36,640
我们找到迈克尔了
We found Michael.

75
00:03:36,670 --> 00:03:39,110
他还是我们的那个迈克尔吗
Is he our Michael?

76
00:03:39,170 --> 00:03:40,690
是的 莎拉
Yes, Sara.

77
00:03:42,760 --> 00:03:45,660
听着 莎拉 他中毒了
Sara, listen, he's been poisoned.

78
00:03:45,700 --> 00:03:46,900
我们觉得是防冻剂中毒
We think it's antifreeze.

79
00:03:46,930 --> 00:03:48,170
他失血过多
He's lost a lot of blood.

80
00:03:48,200 --> 00:03:50,500
需要补血
He needs a lot of blood.

81
00:03:50,540 --> 00:03:51,940
好的
Okay.

82
00:03:51,970 --> 00:03:53,540
如果是防冻剂的话 他还需要很多东西
He needs a lot of things if it's antifreeze.

83
00:03:53,570 --> 00:03:54,810
听着
Listen, uh,

84
00:03:54,840 --> 00:03:56,510
我们要去希腊
we're heading to Greece.

85
00:03:56,540 --> 00:03:58,740
有什么方法能在黑市获得医疗救助么
Is there any way we can get some medical help off the books?

86
00:03:58,780 --> 00:04:00,380
不 不不不不  这事儿你们没法
No, no, no, no, no, this isn't the kind of thing

87
00:04:00,410 --> 00:04:01,950
在黑市干
that you want to do off the books.

88
00:04:01,980 --> 00:04:05,150
听着 林肯 他需要输血
Listen, Lincoln, he's gonna need a transfusion.

89
00:04:05,180 --> 00:04:06,880
迈克尔是B型阴性血 懂么?
Michael's B negative, okay?

90
00:04:06,920 --> 00:04:09,920
大概只有百分之一的人是这种血型
It's maybe one percent of the population with that blood type.

91
00:04:09,960 --> 00:04:11,690
你去那儿是找不到这种血型的
You won't find it where you're going,

92
00:04:11,720 --> 00:04:13,720
他也熬不到你找着
and he won't make it while you look.

93
00:04:15,960 --> 00:04:19,100
除非这种血型自己来找你
Unless it comes to you.

94
00:04:19,130 --> 00:04:20,500
我稍后给你回电
I'll call you back.

95
00:04:22,200 --> 00:04:24,400
嘿 怎么了?
Hey, what's going on?

96
00:04:24,440 --> 00:04:26,000
我...
I, uh...

97
00:04:26,040 --> 00:04:27,910
我得走了
I got to go.

98
00:04:27,940 --> 00:04:29,840
你得走了?
You got to go?

99
00:04:29,880 --> 00:04:31,280
去哪?
‭Go where?

100
00:04:31,310 --> 00:04:32,710
去克里特岛
To Crete.

101
00:04:33,850 --> 00:04:35,250
迈克尔...
Michael, um,

102
00:04:35,280 --> 00:04:36,880
他们找到他了
they found him.

103
00:04:36,920 --> 00:04:38,320
他还活着
He's alive.

104
00:04:38,350 --> 00:04:39,550
他中毒了
He's poisoned.

105
00:04:39,590 --> 00:04:41,950
迈克尔? 你的前夫 迈克尔?
Michael? Your ex, Michael?

106
00:04:41,990 --> 00:04:43,290
是的
Yeah.

107
00:04:43,320 --> 00:04:44,460
等等 等一下
Wait, hold on a second,

108
00:04:44,490 --> 00:04:46,860
他真的还活着?
he really is alive?

109
00:04:46,890 --> 00:04:48,390
他刚刚联系你了?
He contacted you just now?

110
00:04:48,430 --> 00:04:51,860
是的 他需要帮助
Yeah, and, uh, and he needs help,

111
00:04:51,900 --> 00:04:55,970
我觉得我是唯一一个能帮助他的人
and I think I'm the only one that can help him.

112
00:04:57,580 --> 00:05:00,770
我坐飞机比他们坐船去更快
yeah, I can get there faster on a plane than they can on a boat.

113
00:05:00,810 --> 00:05:03,410
喂 莎拉
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Sara?

114
00:05:03,440 --> 00:05:05,280
你不欠他的
Y-You don't owe him that.

115
00:05:05,310 --> 00:05:07,240
你不知道自己将面对什么 太不安全了
You don't know what you'd be walking into. It's not safe.

116
00:05:07,280 --> 00:05:08,650
我会没事的 我别无选择
I'll be fine. I don't have a choice.

117
00:05:08,680 --> 00:05:09,980
我...
I...

118
00:05:10,020 --> 00:05:11,720
这地狱般的一周
This has been a hell of a week.

119
00:05:14,220 --> 00:05:16,120
好吧 我知道你有无数个问题
Okay, look, I know you've got a million questions,

120
00:05:16,160 --> 00:05:17,990
我也一样 好吗
just like I do, okay?

121
00:05:18,020 --> 00:05:20,520
我无法看着我儿子的眼睛
I can't look my son in the eye

122
00:05:20,560 --> 00:05:22,630
告诉他 我明明可以救他父亲
and tell him that I let his father die

123
00:05:22,660 --> 00:05:24,960
却眼睁睁看他死了
when I could've tried to save him.

124
00:05:25,000 --> 00:05:26,330
他从没见过他亲生父亲
A father he's never met.

125
00:05:26,370 --> 00:05:28,930
我不能这么做
I can't do that.

126
00:05:28,970 --> 00:05:30,900
那如果我让你不要去呢
And if I told you not to go?

127
00:05:34,470 --> 00:05:36,110
"如果"是个太沉重的词
"If's" A big word in that sentence.

128
00:05:36,140 --> 00:05:38,280
雅各布 你是在叫我别去吗
Jacob, are you telling me not to go?

129
00:05:41,610 --> 00:05:43,150
不
No.

130
00:05:43,180 --> 00:05:45,150
不 当然不是
No, of course not.

131
00:05:45,180 --> 00:05:47,150
好的
Okay.

132
00:05:58,260 --> 00:06:00,800
不该把她牵扯进来的 林肯
Should've left her out of this, Linc.

133
00:06:00,830 --> 00:06:03,370
闭嘴 你就要见到
Shut up. You're about to see the wife you haven't seen

134
00:06:03,400 --> 00:06:05,040
你七年没见的老婆了
in seven years.

135
00:06:06,970 --> 00:06:08,870
- 我扶你 我扶你 - 你解开缆绳了
- I got you, I got you. - Cast off.

136
00:06:08,910 --> 00:06:10,710
你们已经准备好了
You're ready.

137
00:06:10,740 --> 00:06:12,710
什么意思
What do you mean?

138
00:06:14,650 --> 00:06:18,420
我都不记得自己被关了多久了
Been locked up for longer than I can remember.

139
00:06:18,450 --> 00:06:20,380
在进奥杰吉厄监狱之前 我只有一套公寓 一个脑袋
Before Ogygia, it was my apartment, my head

140
00:06:20,420 --> 00:06:22,450
和一部手机
and my phone.

141
00:06:22,490 --> 00:06:23,990
墙壁将我包围
Walls all around me.

142
00:06:24,020 --> 00:06:27,160
使我看不见外面的世界
Couldn't see the world.

143
00:06:29,860 --> 00:06:31,360
我喜欢这里
I like it here.

144
00:06:31,400 --> 00:06:32,800
没有墙壁
No walls.

145
00:06:32,830 --> 00:06:36,370
我很久没这么自由了
Freedom, like I haven't had in a long time.

146
00:06:36,400 --> 00:06:39,070
我可以重新开始了
I can start over.

147
00:06:39,110 --> 00:06:42,070
除非你说你需要我
And unless you say you need me,

148
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:44,040
不然我更想留下来
I'd like to stay.

149
00:06:44,080 --> 00:06:46,580
贾 你是个自由的人
You're a free man, Ja.

150
00:06:46,610 --> 00:06:48,580
选择权在你
The choice is yours.

151
00:06:49,720 --> 00:06:52,580
我欠你一条命
I owe you my life.

152
00:06:52,620 --> 00:06:54,920
你带我回到了这个世界
You gave me back the world.

153
00:06:58,120 --> 00:06:59,920
让他早日康复 你们一路平安
Get him healthy. Get safe.

154
00:06:59,960 --> 00:07:01,990
嗯 我会的
Yeah, I will.

155
00:07:02,030 --> 00:07:03,830
再见
See you.

156
00:07:07,400 --> 00:07:08,600
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.

157
00:07:08,630 --> 00:07:10,070
我得问个明白
I got to know,

158
00:07:10,100 --> 00:07:13,500
你真的拥有佛莱迪·摩克瑞的骨灰?
you really got Freddie Mercury's ashes?

159
00:07:13,540 --> 00:07:17,270
基思·理查兹真的吸了他亡父的骨灰?
Is it true Keith Richards snorted his dead father's ashes?

160
00:07:17,310 --> 00:07:18,780
我不知道
I don't know.

161
00:07:19,910 --> 00:07:22,110
我也一样
Exactly.

162
00:07:22,150 --> 00:07:23,910
好好活着
Keep alive.

163
00:07:23,950 --> 00:07:26,080
你也是 兄弟
You too, man.

164
00:07:34,330 --> 00:07:36,730
林肯
Linc,

165
00:07:36,760 --> 00:07:38,560
还有多久到希腊?
how far is it to Greece?

166
00:07:38,600 --> 00:07:40,630
十二小时
12 hours.

167
00:07:40,670 --> 00:07:42,230
莎拉十二个小时内就会到
Sara's gonna be there in 12.

168
00:07:42,270 --> 00:07:45,940
我觉得我没有十二个小时可活了
I don't think I have 12 hours in me.

169
00:09:03,460 --> 00:09:06,900
我之前是对的 我们有麻烦了
I was right, we got problems.

170
00:09:06,940 --> 00:09:11,010
很显然 我们昨天去国安局之后
Apparently, State Department is asking questions about 21-Void

171
00:09:11,040 --> 00:09:13,380
国务院就开始问21空洞的事了
after our visit to NSA yesterday.

172
00:09:13,410 --> 00:09:15,280
他们没有任何可靠证据
They have no viable information.

173
00:09:16,410 --> 00:09:18,450
21空洞根本就不存在
21-Void doesn't exist.

174
00:09:18,480 --> 00:09:19,880
波塞冬会做好内部整顿
Poseidon will clean house.

175
00:09:19,920 --> 00:09:22,050
麻烦不会就此消失
The problem's not going away.

176
00:09:22,090 --> 00:09:23,290
那个国务院的特工想在我们降落之后
That State Department agent wants to meet

177
00:09:23,320 --> 00:09:24,790
马上跟我们见面
as soon as we land.

178
00:09:35,470 --> 00:09:37,730
麻烦去哈尼亚
Chania, please?

179
00:09:37,770 --> 00:09:39,030
谢谢
Thank you.

180
00:09:54,490 --> 00:09:56,250
这里很安全
It is safe here.

181
00:09:56,290 --> 00:09:57,820
我来这里的时候才用这个房子
I use when I come.

182
00:09:57,860 --> 00:10:01,460
你能给他弄点吃的吗
You got any food for him?

183
00:10:01,490 --> 00:10:02,660
跟我来 吃的在船上
Come, it's in the boat.

184
00:10:02,690 --> 00:10:05,260
太好了 谢谢
Great, thank you.

185
00:10:05,300 --> 00:10:07,000
给他鼓鼓劲
Keep his spirits up.

186
00:10:07,030 --> 00:10:10,000
知道了 兄弟
All right, man.

187
00:10:12,970 --> 00:10:16,340
噢 天啊
Oh, man.

188
00:10:19,910 --> 00:10:21,810
老兄 你一定得撑住 好吗
Got to hang in there, buddy, huh?

189
00:10:24,450 --> 00:10:28,480
你还有很多事没有告诉我呢
Still got a lot of things to tell me, you know?

190
00:10:31,460 --> 00:10:33,360
你得告诉我为什么我是你的执鞭之手
You gonna tell me why I'm your whip hand.

191
00:10:33,390 --> 00:10:35,520
记得吗?
Remember?

192
00:10:42,730 --> 00:10:44,530
我跟你经历了这么多
I got a lot invested in you.

193
00:10:47,310 --> 00:10:50,140
你现在可不能在我面前死掉啊 迈克尔
You can't die on me now, Michael, you know?

194
00:10:51,510 --> 00:10:54,280
我叫了你迈克尔
Called you Michael.

195
00:10:54,310 --> 00:10:58,950
这是我第一... 第一次知道你的真名
The first... first time I ever really known your name,

196
00:10:58,980 --> 00:11:01,520
虽然我觉得...
even though I feel like...

197
00:11:03,390 --> 00:11:06,190
自打相遇我们就像亲兄弟 你知道吗
I feel like we've been brothers since we met, you know?

198
00:11:11,900 --> 00:11:14,200
而现在 林肯在这儿
You know, with... with Linc here...

199
00:11:17,900 --> 00:11:20,900
这是我第一次觉得自己是个外人
...it was the first time I ever felt like an outsider with you.

200
00:11:20,940 --> 00:11:23,110
就像...
You know, like...

201
00:11:23,140 --> 00:11:25,940
就像我失去了...
like I lost...

202
00:11:25,980 --> 00:11:27,810
我的亲人一样
part of my family or something.

203
00:11:27,850 --> 00:11:31,980
所以迈克尔 你不能死
So, you see, Michael, you can't die.

204
00:11:36,120 --> 00:11:38,420
求你了
Please?

205
00:12:29,410 --> 00:12:32,310
林肯
Linc.

206
00:12:58,340 --> 00:13:00,570
我好想你
I missed you.

207
00:13:09,880 --> 00:13:12,610
我会把你治好的
I'm gonna fix you up.

208
00:13:12,650 --> 00:13:14,780
然后我们再说话 好吗
And then we'll talk, okay?

209
00:13:17,120 --> 00:13:19,490
我会把你治好的
I'm gonna make you okay.

210
00:13:21,630 --> 00:13:23,490
别
No.

211
00:13:24,560 --> 00:13:26,830
别动 没事的
shh, shh, shh, it's okay.

212
00:13:28,030 --> 00:13:30,030
林肯
Hey, Lincoln, uh,

213
00:13:30,070 --> 00:13:32,000
你能帮我把那个衣架拿过来吗
would you pass me that coatrack?

214
00:13:32,040 --> 00:13:34,070
能给我拿张椅子吗
Could I grab the chair, please?

215
00:13:35,840 --> 00:13:37,340
谢谢
Thanks.

216
00:13:58,200 --> 00:14:00,230
我们给他输血
We'll do a transfusion.

217
00:14:04,700 --> 00:14:05,900
我是阴性O型血
I'm O negative.

218
00:14:05,940 --> 00:14:08,500
是万能血
It's the universal donor.

219
00:14:08,540 --> 00:14:11,410
这是他唯一能接受的血型
Turns out it's the only other blood type I could've given him.

220
00:14:14,040 --> 00:14:16,040
也许这就是命运 对吧
Maybe there's something to destiny, huh?

221
00:14:20,180 --> 00:14:23,190
他会活下去吗
Is he gonna live?

222
00:14:23,220 --> 00:14:25,890
会的
Yeah.

223
00:14:25,920 --> 00:14:28,190
他会活下去的
Yeah, he'll live.

224
00:14:28,230 --> 00:14:30,830
给他几小时
Give him a couple hours.

225
00:14:30,860 --> 00:14:33,260
他很坚强
He's strong.

226
00:14:36,500 --> 00:14:39,800
我们... 我们让你俩单独待会
We'll, uh... we'll give you a minute.

227
00:14:39,840 --> 00:14:41,740
好
Yeah.

228
00:14:41,770 --> 00:14:44,940
我就在你身边
I'm right here.

229
00:14:44,980 --> 00:14:46,710
我就在你身边
I'm right here.

230
00:14:51,750 --> 00:14:54,280
我们得想办法离开这个岛
We need to work out a way to get off this island.

231
00:15:00,960 --> 00:15:03,590
我之前
What I said...

232
00:15:03,630 --> 00:15:07,260
说你...
um, about you...

233
00:15:07,300 --> 00:15:09,600
是我错了
I was wrong.

234
00:15:13,370 --> 00:15:14,800
任何人能有个像你这样的哥哥
A man would be lucky to have a brother

235
00:15:14,840 --> 00:15:16,910
都是三生有幸
cares as much as you, you know?

236
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,740
有这样的妻子
Wife like that...

237
00:15:22,510 --> 00:15:24,610
这样的家庭
...family.

238
00:15:27,650 --> 00:15:29,720
这不是运气使然
I wouldn't call it luck.

239
00:15:29,750 --> 00:15:32,450
你跟我们共患难
You've been through what we've been through.

240
00:15:32,490 --> 00:15:34,290
你现在已经是我们的家人了
You're family now.

241
00:15:37,860 --> 00:15:39,230
我得为此喝一杯
I'll drink to that.

242
00:15:39,260 --> 00:15:41,660
好
Yeah.

243
00:15:43,070 --> 00:15:44,670
坐飞机真的是不可能了?
Flying's really out of the question?

244
00:15:44,700 --> 00:15:45,830
是的
Yeah.

245
00:15:45,870 --> 00:15:49,770
机场比医院还行不通
Airports are worse than hospitals.

246
00:15:49,810 --> 00:15:52,810
而且肯尼尔·奥提斯这个名字招人耳目
And once the name Kaniel Outis is radioactive,

247
00:15:52,840 --> 00:15:54,910
他们看见他就会立马杀了他的
they'll shoot him on sight.

248
00:15:56,180 --> 00:15:58,510
那再找一艘船?
So another boat?

249
00:15:58,550 --> 00:16:00,550
横渡大西洋?
Across the Atlantic?

250
00:16:00,580 --> 00:16:05,790
我虽不是个水手 却也知道这港口没船能
Mm, I'm no sailor, but I know that no boat in that harbor

251
00:16:05,820 --> 00:16:08,290
走那么远
is gonna get us that far.

252
00:16:08,330 --> 00:16:09,830
我们需要一艘大船
We need a big boat.

253
00:16:11,500 --> 00:16:15,930
一艘不介意装放射性货物的船
One that doesn't mind a radioactive cargo, you know?

254
00:16:30,310 --> 00:16:34,020
你们好 我想跟进我们上次的谈话
Hey there, I wanted to follow up on our conversation.

255
00:16:34,050 --> 00:16:35,750
很明显中情局和国务院
Obviously, the CIA and State,

256
00:16:35,790 --> 00:16:37,790
我们一直在共享关于肯尼尔·奥提斯的信息
we've been sharing information on Kaniel Outis,

257
00:16:37,820 --> 00:16:40,020
但我要问你们的是
but my question for you is:

258
00:16:40,060 --> 00:16:41,720
奥提斯杀了阿布·阿米尔
Outis killed Abu Ramal,

259
00:16:41,760 --> 00:16:44,130
为这个国家做了贡献
did the country a service.

260
00:16:44,160 --> 00:16:46,760
那为什么你们昨天在国安局还
So why were you still at NSA yesterday,

261
00:16:46,800 --> 00:16:48,800
想把他杀了?
trying to kill him?

262
00:16:48,830 --> 00:16:50,830
我们先走出停机坪吧
Why don't we get off the tarmac?

263
00:16:50,870 --> 00:16:53,170
然后我们会告诉你我们的调查研究
We'll share what we can about our investigation.

264
00:16:54,540 --> 00:16:57,240
这完全是官僚主义的沟通不畅
This is all just bureaucratic miscommunication.

265
00:16:57,270 --> 00:16:59,470
我们可以解决
We can iron it out.

266
00:16:59,510 --> 00:17:01,840
告诉你们 我们和中情局联系过了
So you know, we checked with CIA.

267
00:17:01,880 --> 00:17:05,150
中情局并没有批准你们昨天造访国安局
The CIA didn't sanction your visit to NSA yesterday.

268
00:17:05,180 --> 00:17:06,950
甚至没人知道你们去了那里
No one even knew you were there.

269
00:17:06,980 --> 00:17:09,480
所以你们到底在为谁效力?
Who are you working for, really?

270
00:17:09,520 --> 00:17:12,020
你们为什么想把肯尼尔·奥提斯干掉?
And why were you trying to take out Kaniel Outis?

271
00:17:20,630 --> 00:17:23,100
我从没想到我会在见到你
Never thought I'd see this face again.

272
00:17:23,130 --> 00:17:25,600
你本不应该见到我
You weren't supposed to.

273
00:17:27,200 --> 00:17:29,070
为什么?
Why?

274
00:17:30,910 --> 00:17:34,340
我会告诉你你想知道的一切
I'll tell you everything you want to know.

275
00:17:34,380 --> 00:17:36,880
但首先 我需要你给我一样东西
But first, I need something from you.

276
00:17:36,910 --> 00:17:38,750
什么都可以
Anything.

277
00:17:40,380 --> 00:17:43,290
给我一张我儿子的照片
A picture of my son.

278
00:17:46,460 --> 00:17:48,290
我们昨天没有去国安局
We weren't at NSA yesterday.

279
00:17:48,330 --> 00:17:50,530
我是说 你们搞错了
I'm telling you, this is a mistake.

280
00:17:50,560 --> 00:17:52,160
你跟我说谎才是搞错了
And it's a mistake to lie to me.

281
00:17:52,200 --> 00:17:53,930
我可以起诉你
I can have you prosecuted.

282
00:17:53,960 --> 00:17:57,870
我在国安局有熟人 她给了我证据
I have a contact at the NSA and she gave me proof.

283
00:17:57,900 --> 00:18:00,640
你没有给他起名叫小迈克尔吧?
You're not calling him Junior, are you?

284
00:18:00,670 --> 00:18:03,810
我跟你我保证 我肯定不会这样叫他
I promised you I would never do that.

285
00:18:05,040 --> 00:18:06,980
他是第一个很好的孩子
He's an amazing kid.

286
00:18:08,610 --> 00:18:10,380
跟你一个模子刻出来的
He's just like you.

287
00:18:19,190 --> 00:18:20,960
怎么了?
What's wrong?

288
00:18:33,100 --> 00:18:34,640
是他
It's him.

289
00:18:40,280 --> 00:18:42,510
你的丈夫
Your husband.

290
00:18:42,550 --> 00:18:44,610
雅各布?
Jacob?

291
00:18:44,650 --> 00:18:46,920
雅各布
Jacob.

292
00:18:54,190 --> 00:18:56,490
雅各布就是波塞冬
Jacob is Poseidon.

293
00:19:04,400 --> 00:19:06,530
我知道 我没疯
I knewt. I wasn't crazy.

294
00:19:06,630 --> 00:19:10,030
我发现他撒谎了 但是他...他...
I caught him lying, but he-he--

295
00:19:10,140 --> 00:19:11,670
哦 天哪 他掩饰得太好了
oh, God, he covered it so well.

296
00:19:11,770 --> 00:19:14,710
他..人一直很诚实而且当时还受伤了
He was... honest and hurt,

297
00:19:14,810 --> 00:19:16,340
我就相信了他说的话
and I bought it.

298
00:19:16,440 --> 00:19:17,780
他是谁?
Who is he?

299
00:19:17,880 --> 00:19:19,540
到底?
Really?

300
00:19:19,650 --> 00:19:23,010
他是中情局特工 是个卧底
He's a CIA operative, deep cover.

301
00:19:23,120 --> 00:19:25,280
他在主管运行这个叫“21空洞”的组织
He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.

302
00:19:25,380 --> 00:19:27,650
但这跟你有什么关系?
What does this have to do with you?

303
00:19:27,750 --> 00:19:30,390
他看上了我的本事
He targeted me for my skills,

304
00:19:30,490 --> 00:19:31,960
勒索我
blackmailed me.

305
00:19:32,060 --> 00:19:34,430
他说如果我不同意为他工作
He told me if I didn't agree to come work for him,

306
00:19:34,530 --> 00:19:36,230
他会来追捕你和林肯
he'd go after you and Linc,

307
00:19:36,330 --> 00:19:38,700
把你们俩都送进监狱
put you both in jail.

308
00:19:39,250 --> 00:19:41,250
然后他证明给我看了
And then he proved it to me.

309
00:19:43,390 --> 00:19:45,820
他说我将再也见不到你们俩
He said I could never see either one of you again.

310
00:19:46,730 --> 00:19:48,520
包括迈克
Or Mike.

311
00:19:48,620 --> 00:19:50,560
逼我伪造了我的死亡
Made me fake my death.

312
00:19:50,660 --> 00:19:53,190
然后他利用了我
And then he just used me.

313
00:19:53,300 --> 00:19:54,730
他娶了我
He married me.

314
00:19:54,830 --> 00:19:56,560
如果我知道他是你丈夫 我发誓...
If I'd known he was your husband, I swear...

315
00:19:56,670 --> 00:19:57,660
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no,

316
00:19:57,770 --> 00:19:59,700
这不怪你
this is not on you.

317
00:19:59,800 --> 00:20:01,840
我..
I...

318
00:20:03,640 --> 00:20:05,910
为什么是现在? 你为什么要现在回来?
Why now? Why did you come back now?

319
00:20:06,010 --> 00:20:08,110
那张折纸...
The origami...

320
00:20:09,880 --> 00:20:12,550
4年前 他背叛了我
Four years ago, he betrayed me

321
00:20:12,650 --> 00:20:15,180
现在我知道为什么了
and now I know why.

322
00:20:15,280 --> 00:20:18,690
他想让我退出
He wanted me out of the way...

323
00:20:18,790 --> 00:20:20,520
然后他就能得到你了
so he could have you.

324
00:20:21,490 --> 00:20:23,790
他怎么背叛的你?
How did he betray you?

325
00:20:23,890 --> 00:20:26,060
他安排了一次会议
He set a meeting.

326
00:20:26,160 --> 00:20:28,960
我们本来应该讨论我的下一个任务
We were supposed to discuss my next assignment.

327
00:20:29,060 --> 00:20:31,600
但他没有告诉我
What he didn't tell me was that

328
00:20:31,700 --> 00:20:33,070
我们要见一个叫哈兰·盖恩斯的人
we were meeting a man named Harlan Gaines,

329
00:20:33,170 --> 00:20:35,970
中情局的副局长
a deputy director of the CIA.

330
00:20:36,070 --> 00:20:38,170
盖恩斯当时正在调查21空洞
Gaines was investigating 21-Void.

331
00:20:38,270 --> 00:20:40,470
找这背后的叛徒
Looking for the traitor behind it.

332
00:20:40,580 --> 00:20:44,610
那个时候我意识到我干的事没有被中情局批准过
That's when I knew my work wasn't sanctioned by the CIA.

333
00:20:44,710 --> 00:20:47,850
波塞冬那天晚上开枪杀了盖恩斯
Poseidon shot and killed Gaines that night,

334
00:20:47,950 --> 00:20:49,980
阻止他调查
to stop the investigation.

335
00:20:53,560 --> 00:20:54,860
他让我把尸体拖走
He told me to move the body,

336
00:20:54,960 --> 00:20:57,290
伪装成什么都没有发生过的样子
make it look like it never happened.

337
00:20:57,390 --> 00:20:59,560
我看过关于这件事的照片 他们太可恶
I've seen the photos of that part, they're damning.

338
00:20:59,660 --> 00:21:02,300
他选了正好拍到我拖动盖恩斯尸体的那断录像
He chose images that showed me moving Gaines' body,

339
00:21:02,400 --> 00:21:05,470
删除了对他不利的片段
eliminated the ones that incriminated himself.

340
00:21:05,570 --> 00:21:08,540
我知道我被陷害了
I knew I was being set up.

341
00:21:08,640 --> 00:21:10,470
他当时对我控制得越来越死
He was tightening his control over me,

342
00:21:10,570 --> 00:21:13,840
但我什么也做不了
but there was nothing I could do.

343
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:16,810
至少 他是这么想的
At least, that's what he thought.

344
00:21:16,910 --> 00:21:19,610
当我知道波塞冬不按指示行事
When I knew Poseidon had gone rogue

345
00:21:19,720 --> 00:21:22,080
并且活动于中情局工作范围之外
and was operating outside the CIA,

346
00:21:22,180 --> 00:21:24,680
我开始计划回到你身边的
that's when I started my plan to get back to you.

347
00:21:25,620 --> 00:21:26,900
但你没回来
You're not.

348
00:21:26,990 --> 00:21:28,600
别的人替代了你...
Some other man has your--

349
00:21:28,990 --> 00:21:30,760
你的脸 你的过去 你全部的生活
your face, your past, your whole life.

350
00:21:30,860 --> 00:21:33,530
萨拉 这是计划中的一部分
Sara, there is a plan to make this right,

351
00:21:33,630 --> 00:21:36,360
为了保护我们的家庭
to protect our family.

352
00:21:38,500 --> 00:21:41,200
迈克尔 他现在跟我们的儿子在一起
Michael, he's with our son right now.

353
00:21:41,300 --> 00:21:44,470
他跟迈克在一起
He's with Mike.

354
00:21:44,570 --> 00:21:47,440
我  我得走了
I, uh, look, I have to go.

355
00:21:51,180 --> 00:21:52,980
诺亚 你能给我们建艘船吗?
Hey, Noah, you gonna build us a boat?

356
00:21:53,080 --> 00:21:56,720
不 我能搞个更好的过来
Nope. I'm gonna do one better.

357
00:21:56,820 --> 00:21:58,390
你给谁打电话呢?
Who you calling?

358
00:21:59,520 --> 00:22:02,040
一个真的有船的朋友
A friend who actually has a boat.

359
00:22:11,200 --> 00:22:12,600
喂?
Hello?

360
00:22:12,700 --> 00:22:13,800
苏克雷 是我
Sucre, it's me.

361
00:22:13,900 --> 00:22:15,840
林肯? 我以为你会在中东
Linc? I thought the Middle East

362
00:22:15,940 --> 00:22:17,100
回不来了呢 哥们儿
was gonna swallow you up, man.

363
00:22:17,210 --> 00:22:20,010
迈克尔在哪? 你找到他了吗？
Where's Michael? Did you find him?

364
00:22:20,110 --> 00:22:22,080
听着 这就是我打电话来的原因
Listen, that's why I'm calling.

365
00:22:22,180 --> 00:22:23,740
我们在克里特岛
We're on the island of Crete.

366
00:22:23,850 --> 00:22:25,680
我们需要悄悄偷渡回美国
We need a low profile ride back to the States.

367
00:22:25,780 --> 00:22:27,350
我愿意帮忙
I would love to help,

368
00:22:27,450 --> 00:22:29,150
但我们之间隔了大半个地球 哥们
but we're on the other side of the world, brother.

369
00:22:29,250 --> 00:22:30,820
我们刚在摩洛哥卸完货
We just dropped a load in Morocco.

370
00:22:30,920 --> 00:22:33,320
你在说什么? 摩洛哥跟克里特离得很近啊
What are you talking about? Morocco's near Crete.

371
00:22:33,420 --> 00:22:36,190
是 我知道 当然是这样
Yeah, I know, of course it is,

372
00:22:36,290 --> 00:22:38,430
但我的意思是这不是我的船
but what I mean is it's not my ship.

373
00:22:38,530 --> 00:22:41,260
好吧  现在这个船把捎带我们回去要多少钱
Yeah, but what would it cost to hitch a ride?

374
00:22:41,360 --> 00:22:42,960
我们没法捎带你
You can't hitch a ride.

375
00:22:43,070 --> 00:22:44,700
你们必须租下整艘船
You have to rent the whole ship.

376
00:22:44,800 --> 00:22:47,130
老板要价5万 林肯
The boss charges 50K a leg, Linc.

377
00:22:47,240 --> 00:22:49,370
如果你们想要回美国 5万
You want to get back to the States, it's 50K.

378
00:22:49,470 --> 00:22:50,600
5万?
50k?

379
00:22:50,710 --> 00:22:52,910
我们只是想回国而已
We're just trying to get home.

380
00:22:53,010 --> 00:22:55,010
你知道我们没有那么多钱
You know we don't have that kind of cash.

381
00:22:56,650 --> 00:22:58,010
现在有了
You do now.

382
00:22:59,310 --> 00:23:00,750
这个 这是我祖母给我的
Here, this was my grandmother's.

383
00:23:00,850 --> 00:23:02,150
这个传家宝肯定值那么多钱了
It's an heirloom worth at least that.

384
00:23:06,490 --> 00:23:08,790
这是它最大的用处了
I can't think of a better use for it.

385
00:23:09,690 --> 00:23:11,390
谢谢你
Thank you.

386
00:23:11,490 --> 00:23:15,760
我们有钱了 苏克雷 来克里特
We got it, Sucre. Get to Crete.

387
00:23:17,570 --> 00:23:19,800
在他怀疑你可能发现他的真实身份之前
He's not gonna hurt Mike,

388
00:23:19,820 --> 00:23:22,440
他不会伤害迈克的
not unless he suspects you know who he really is.

389
00:23:22,540 --> 00:23:23,900
如果你揭穿他的真实面目
If you remove his mask,

390
00:23:24,010 --> 00:23:25,570
他可能就会出手了
he'll lash out.

391
00:23:25,670 --> 00:23:27,340
你比我更了解他
You know him better than I do.

392
00:23:27,440 --> 00:23:29,110
关键是 没人了解他
That's the point, no one knows him.

393
00:23:29,210 --> 00:23:30,910
所以 我该怎么办
So, what do I do?

394
00:23:31,010 --> 00:23:33,550
你跟他玩下去 你装成什么都不知道
You play his game. You wear your own mask.

395
00:23:33,650 --> 00:23:36,580
一旦发现有机会能带着迈克逃跑
As soon as you get a chance to get away with Mike,

396
00:23:36,690 --> 00:23:40,220
赶快跑 消失
you take it, disappear.

397
00:23:40,320 --> 00:23:42,420
我会尽快赶回美国
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.

398
00:23:42,520 --> 00:23:45,130
找到你
I'll find you.

399
00:23:45,230 --> 00:23:46,890
你看起来好多了
You're looking better.

400
00:23:47,000 --> 00:23:48,730
脸色还是有点差 但是好多了
A little grayer, but better.

401
00:23:48,830 --> 00:23:51,870
我有你这个出色的医生在身边
I have an amazing doctor on call.

402
00:23:58,670 --> 00:24:01,540
我会伪装好
I will wear the mask.

403
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:04,080
我会跟他玩下去
I will play his game...

404
00:24:04,180 --> 00:24:07,850
但如果他伤害我们的儿子我就杀了他
and if he hurts our son I'll kill him.

405
00:24:10,750 --> 00:24:12,250
我不能...
I can't...

406
00:24:29,440 --> 00:24:32,870
一定要回到我们身边
Please come back to us.

407
00:24:49,690 --> 00:24:51,590
她一个人离开克里特岛了
She's leaving Crete alone,

408
00:24:51,690 --> 00:24:54,830
留下了迈克尔 说明迈克尔肯定会在接下来的
which means she left Outis behind, and he'll try to follow,

409
00:24:54,930 --> 00:24:56,700
一两天之内回到美国
return to the U.S. In the next day or two.

410
00:24:56,700 --> 00:24:58,670
-谁打的电话? -他要么坐船要么坐飞机 
Who called? It can only be by ship or plane, so plaster his face

411
00:24:58,690 --> 00:25:01,940
所以把他的样貌给所有的港口 海关报备
on all maritime and air channels,

412
00:25:01,950 --> 00:25:03,540
在接下来的48小时
focusing on all vessels departing from Crete

413
00:25:03,640 --> 00:25:04,600
重点注意从克里特岛来的船
in the next 48 hours.

414
00:25:04,710 --> 00:25:06,370
他肯定在其中一艘上
He's got to be on one.

415
00:25:06,480 --> 00:25:08,810
- 不能让他入境 - 雅各布?
He can't make it back inside the country. Jacob?

416
00:25:09,850 --> 00:25:11,780
你在跟妈妈打电话吗?
Was that Mommy?

417
00:25:14,180 --> 00:25:18,390
是的 你妈妈快回来了
Yes. Mommy's on her way home.

418
00:25:29,550 --> 00:25:31,550
迈克·斯科菲尔德
Michael Scofield.

419
00:25:32,890 --> 00:25:35,550
兄弟 你比别人多了好几条命啊
My man, you got more lives than anyone.

420
00:25:36,790 --> 00:25:38,420
我觉得快要用光了
Think I might've used them all up.

421
00:25:39,290 --> 00:25:40,890
真他妈的死而复生了
A damn phoenix.

422
00:25:40,930 --> 00:25:42,530
难以置信
I can't believe it.

423
00:25:42,560 --> 00:25:44,100
快给我说说
I want to hear every damn thing

424
00:25:44,130 --> 00:25:45,830
你死后发生的所有的的事情
that's happened to you since you died.

425
00:25:45,870 --> 00:25:47,530
兄弟 你又活了?
Papi, you're alive?

426
00:25:50,670 --> 00:25:52,170
机长贪得无厌是个狗娘养的
The skipper is a corrupt bastard.

427
00:25:52,210 --> 00:25:53,770
别和他打交道 他手里有枪
Don't mess with him. He's got guns in the hold,

428
00:25:53,810 --> 00:25:56,810
- 还有各种走私的货物 - 船长
- all kinds of contraband. - Captain.

429
00:25:59,050 --> 00:26:00,850
这是我说起过的货物
Here's the cargo I was telling you about.

430
00:26:00,880 --> 00:26:02,710
付钱
Pay up.

431
00:26:02,750 --> 00:26:04,920
我要的五万块呢?
Where's the 50K?

432
00:26:04,950 --> 00:26:06,690
在这儿
Here.

433
00:26:06,720 --> 00:26:09,590
我说过要现金的
I said cash.

434
00:26:09,620 --> 00:26:11,920
这是蓝宝石 六克拉
It's a sapphire, six carats,

435
00:26:11,960 --> 00:26:15,560
无缝宝石 四周是二点五克拉的钻石斜面
flawless, surrounded by 2.5 carats of bezeled diamonds.

436
00:26:15,600 --> 00:26:17,500
市价是十二万五千
Street value is 125K.

437
00:26:17,530 --> 00:26:21,930
你可以半价抵押还有盈余
You can pawn it for half that and still make a profit.

438
00:26:30,210 --> 00:26:31,380
如果是个假的
If it's fake,

439
00:26:31,410 --> 00:26:33,950
就把那你扔海里
you go under the sea.

440
00:26:36,420 --> 00:26:39,350
到船上找你是最后的希望了 朋友
A boat is the last place I expected to find you, buddy.

441
00:26:39,390 --> 00:26:40,950
我以为你不喜欢水
I thought you hated the water.

442
00:26:40,990 --> 00:26:44,220
是 你记得没错 不过我有犯罪记录
Yeah, you remember, but I got a record.

443
00:26:44,260 --> 00:26:46,890
没有什么人愿意冒险雇我
Not a lot of employers lined up to take a chance on me.

444
00:26:46,930 --> 00:26:49,330
还有 这艘船给了我机会
Besides, this ship provides opportunities

445
00:26:49,360 --> 00:26:51,060
搞些副业...
for my side business...

446
00:26:51,100 --> 00:26:53,030
这才是我到这艘船上的真正原因
which is the real reason I'm on this boat.

447
00:26:53,070 --> 00:26:55,000
这宝贝...
This baby...

448
00:26:55,040 --> 00:26:57,170
承载在我的所有积蓄
houses my entire life savings.

449
00:26:57,200 --> 00:26:59,540
和你们说 这是个巨大的生意
I'm telling you, it's gonna be huge.

450
00:26:59,570 --> 00:27:02,240
我几个月前把这些带上来的
I'm a few months away from putting all this behind me.

451
00:27:02,280 --> 00:27:04,510
算你们幸运 让你们见识下
If you guys are lucky, I'll let you guys

452
00:27:04,550 --> 00:27:07,080
我们的姑娘们
take one of my ladies for a spin.

453
00:27:09,480 --> 00:27:10,920
嗯?
Huh?

454
00:27:11,820 --> 00:27:13,820
什么 性爱娃娃?
What, sex dolls?

455
00:27:13,850 --> 00:27:15,050
错 有点档次好吗 兄弟
No, have some class, man.

456
00:27:15,090 --> 00:27:16,860
准确的说法是充气娃娃 高品质的
The term is inflatables, high quality,

457
00:27:16,890 --> 00:27:18,620
很贵的 超仿真
expensive, very lifelike.

458
00:27:20,690 --> 00:27:23,260
嗯?
Huh?

459
00:27:40,680 --> 00:27:41,880
嗨 亲爱的
Hey, honey.

460
00:27:41,920 --> 00:27:44,050
嗨 你好啊
Hey, you.

461
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:01,270
迈克在哪儿?
Where's Mike?

462
00:28:01,300 --> 00:28:03,670
睡着了
Asleep.

463
00:28:03,700 --> 00:28:04,700
小朋友今天玩得很嗨
Kid had a big day.

464
00:28:06,370 --> 00:28:08,540
但是 最要紧的是
Most important, though,

465
00:28:08,580 --> 00:28:10,080
迈克尔怎么样了?
how's Michael?

466
00:28:10,110 --> 00:28:12,180
你能帮到他吗?
Were you able to help him?

467
00:28:12,210 --> 00:28:16,720
我到那儿的时候他差不多已经死了
I mean, he was barely alive when I got there.

468
00:28:16,750 --> 00:28:20,390
他 那时一直在昏睡
He, uh, slept most of the time.

469
00:28:20,420 --> 00:28:22,320
我... 我尽我所能挽救他 ...
I... I did what I could for him. I, uh...

470
00:28:22,360 --> 00:28:26,290
我让他状况稳定了下来 但是他变了
I stabilized him, but he's changed.

471
00:28:26,330 --> 00:28:30,600
他 ... 他变得不是昔日我认识的那个人了
He, uh... he's just not the guy I knew.

472
00:28:30,630 --> 00:28:33,530
他们把我送到了机场 就这样
Hmm. ‭So, they dropped me at the airport and that was that.

473
00:28:33,570 --> 00:28:35,630
他们?
They?

474
00:28:35,670 --> 00:28:37,800
林肯和其他人
Linc and some other guy.

475
00:28:45,080 --> 00:28:47,410
迈克?
Mike?

476
00:28:49,780 --> 00:28:51,320
迈克在哪儿?
Where's Mike?

477
00:28:51,350 --> 00:28:53,150
- 你说他睡了 - 是睡了
You said that he was asleep. ‭He is...

478
00:28:53,190 --> 00:28:55,690
他在朋友家过夜
at a friend's house, a sleepover.

479
00:28:55,720 --> 00:28:58,560
好 哪个朋友?
Okay. Which friend?

480
00:28:58,590 --> 00:28:59,890
他在帕特里克家里
He's at Patrick's house.

481
00:29:03,530 --> 00:29:05,700
你祖母的戒指哪儿去了?
What happened to your grandmother's ring?

482
00:29:06,770 --> 00:29:09,170
我真是个笨蛋
I'm such an idiot.

483
00:29:09,200 --> 00:29:11,070
我在去的路上为了安全把它摘下来
I took it off on the way over for safekeeping,

484
00:29:11,100 --> 00:29:13,040
我不想它被偷走
cause I didn't want it to get stolen,

485
00:29:13,070 --> 00:29:16,640
然后我回来的路上再想找它就不见了
then when I looked for it on the way back it was gone.

486
00:29:16,680 --> 00:29:20,480
我在飞机场喊了出来差点被人从飞机上扔出来
Screamed so loud they nearly threw me off the flight.

487
00:29:50,340 --> 00:29:51,780
喂?
Yeah?

488
00:29:51,810 --> 00:29:54,350
我和我们在五角大楼的人谈过了
We spoke to our man at the Pentagon.

489
00:29:54,380 --> 00:29:55,950
一份海军警报刚刚发出
A naval alert just went out.

490
00:29:55,980 --> 00:29:58,080
肯尼尔·奥提斯被发现
Kaniel Outis has been located

491
00:29:58,120 --> 00:30:00,690
在地中海的一艘货轮上
on a cargo ship in the Mediterranean.

492
00:30:00,720 --> 00:30:02,650
是那艘船的船长报告的
It was reported by the ship's captain.

493
00:30:02,690 --> 00:30:04,320
海军会采取什么行动?
What's the navy gonna do about it?

494
00:30:04,360 --> 00:30:06,420
最近的支援登陆艇战斗船
The nearest LCS combat craft

495
00:30:06,460 --> 00:30:08,260
正在移动介入
is moving to engage.

496
00:30:08,300 --> 00:30:09,830
海豹突击队已部署
SEAL team's been deployed.

497
00:30:09,860 --> 00:30:11,430
给他们的命令是?
Orders?

498
00:30:11,470 --> 00:30:14,870
搜寻并摧毁肯尼尔·奥提斯
To seek and destroy Kaniel Outis.

499
00:30:14,900 --> 00:30:16,300
好
Good.

500
00:30:16,340 --> 00:30:18,070
我们的任务是放出消息
We've done our job getting the message out.

501
00:30:18,110 --> 00:30:21,170
接下来留给海豹突击队完成他们的任务
Now it's time for the SEALs to do theirs.

502
00:30:21,210 --> 00:30:24,010
上帝
My God.

503
00:30:25,150 --> 00:30:27,380
你这是经历了炼狱啊 朋友
You've been through hell, my friend.

504
00:30:30,520 --> 00:30:32,250
要有信心 兄弟
Have some faith, papi.

505
00:30:32,290 --> 00:30:34,820
谢谢 兄弟
Thanks, papi.

506
00:30:36,320 --> 00:30:37,360
你怎么样 林肯
What about you, Linc?

507
00:30:38,760 --> 00:30:40,760
我认为林肯有了一个秘密女友
I think Linc's got a secret girlfriend,

508
00:30:40,790 --> 00:30:42,760
导航员姑娘
the pilot lady.

509
00:30:42,800 --> 00:30:44,130
她不是我的女友
She's not my lady.

510
00:30:44,160 --> 00:30:46,700
也许苏克雷会给你介绍个性爱娃娃
Maybe Sucre will set you up with one of his sex dolls.

511
00:30:46,730 --> 00:30:48,030
他们不是娃娃 兄弟
They're not dolls, man.

512
00:30:48,070 --> 00:30:49,570
哦 抱歉 是充气娃娃
Oh, sorry, inflatables.

513
00:30:49,600 --> 00:30:51,270
我说 换个话题吧 拜托
Look, let's just change the subject, please.

514
00:30:51,300 --> 00:30:54,040
你们知道的 应该要说点能解决问题的
You know, might be something to be said for settling down.

515
00:30:54,070 --> 00:30:57,480
没错 嗯... 这副牌可不会给我们答案
Right, well... that's not in the cards.

516
00:31:03,880 --> 00:31:05,880
从外面锁住了
It's locked from the outside.

517
00:31:05,920 --> 00:31:06,950
他们出卖你了
They made you.

518
00:31:06,990 --> 00:31:08,950
你真的是被通缉的恐怖分子
You really are a wanted terrorist.

519
00:31:08,990 --> 00:31:10,190
他刚刚说的你他妈的都听到哪儿去了?
What did the hell did you think he was saying?

520
00:31:10,220 --> 00:31:11,160
我以为就是打个比方
I thought it was an analogy.

521
00:31:11,190 --> 00:31:12,420
哦 看在上帝的份上
Oh, for God's sake.

522
00:31:12,460 --> 00:31:13,860
没有其他办法
There's no other way

523
00:31:13,890 --> 00:31:16,030
从船舱里出去
out of this cabin.

524
00:31:19,830 --> 00:31:24,540
所有船员都到顶层甲板上来 手举起来
All crew to the top deck. All hands up.

525
00:31:24,570 --> 00:31:27,010
照做否则我们将会开枪射击
Comply or be fired on.

526
00:31:27,040 --> 00:31:30,880
这艘船现在被美国海军控制
This ship is now under the control of the U.S. Navy.

527
00:31:30,910 --> 00:31:31,780
准备好我们将要登船
Prepared to be boarded.

528
00:31:31,810 --> 00:31:33,450
我们有伴儿了
We got company.

529
00:31:33,480 --> 00:31:34,710
我说咱们跳下去吧
I say we jump.

530
00:31:34,750 --> 00:31:35,880
下去还有很远呢
That's a long way down.

531
00:31:35,920 --> 00:31:37,120
这是唯一的通路
It's the only way out.

532
00:31:37,130 --> 00:31:37,940
太远了
It's too far.

533
00:31:37,980 --> 00:31:39,540
我有个想法...
I have an idea...

534
00:31:41,320 --> 00:31:44,080
...可是会挺痛的
...but it's gonna hurt.

535
00:32:02,400 --> 00:32:04,300
哈啰?
Hello?

536
00:32:04,340 --> 00:32:06,140
海瑟 是我 听好 我不能多说
Hey, Heather, it's me. Listen, I can't talk,

537
00:32:06,170 --> 00:32:08,340
可是我想让你现在就去接走迈克 可以吗?
but I need you to go pick up Mike right now, okay?

538
00:32:08,380 --> 00:32:09,810
你知道帕特里克·门罗住哪里吗?
Do you know where Patrick Monroe lives?

539
00:32:09,840 --> 00:32:10,810
知道
Yeah.

540
00:32:10,840 --> 00:32:12,010
那就好
Okay.

541
00:32:12,050 --> 00:32:13,550
听着 我迟点会解释的
Listen, I'll explain later.

542
00:32:13,580 --> 00:32:15,410
不要带他回来了
Don't bring him back here, okay?

543
00:32:15,450 --> 00:32:17,550
让他跟着你 我一搞定就会过来
Keep him with you. I'll be over as soon as I can.

544
00:32:17,580 --> 00:32:18,880
你可以帮我做到吗?
Can you do that for me?

545
00:32:18,920 --> 00:32:21,150
呃 好 我现在就去
Uh, yeah. Uh, I'll leave right now.

546
00:32:21,190 --> 00:32:22,520
一切都还好吧?
I-I-Is everything okay?

547
00:32:22,560 --> 00:32:23,620
不好
No.

548
00:32:32,030 --> 00:32:33,370
出发
Go.

549
00:32:35,840 --> 00:32:37,770
六点钟方向 其他的跟我走
Six. The rest with me.

550
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:42,270
走
Go.

551
00:32:48,450 --> 00:32:51,350
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.

552
00:32:53,690 --> 00:32:55,150
走 走
Go, go.

553
00:33:02,700 --> 00:33:04,730
我走左边 你右边
I'll go left, you right.

554
00:33:13,340 --> 00:33:14,370
他们从窗口逃走了!
They went out the window!

555
00:33:14,410 --> 00:33:15,670
他们从窗口逃走了
They went out the window!

556
00:33:15,710 --> 00:33:17,980
你看到什么?
What do you see?

557
00:33:18,010 --> 00:33:19,510
看不到他们
No visual.

558
00:33:20,810 --> 00:33:23,850
阿尔法一号 阿尔法二号立刻去左舷
Alpha One, Alpha Two to portside, now.

559
00:33:23,880 --> 00:33:26,380
收到
Copy that.

560
00:33:28,320 --> 00:33:29,690
好了!
Okay!

561
00:33:29,720 --> 00:33:32,390
松...给我松绑!
Take... Take it off!

562
00:33:32,430 --> 00:33:33,430
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?

563
00:33:33,460 --> 00:33:35,260
费尔南多
Fernando.

564
00:33:35,300 --> 00:33:36,860
费尔南多·苏克雷
Fernando Sucre.

565
00:33:36,900 --> 00:33:39,000
我是一名船员 你可以看下班表
I'm a member of this crew. Check the roster, man.

566
00:33:39,030 --> 00:33:40,830
我和这事一点关系都没有
I got no part in any of this.

567
00:33:40,870 --> 00:33:44,740
在班表上找一下费尔南多·苏克雷
Check the roster for Fernando Sucre.

568
00:33:46,210 --> 00:33:48,830
疑犯是在班表上
Suspect seems to check out.

569
00:33:48,930 --> 00:33:50,380
带他去驾驶室
Take him to the bridge.

570
00:33:50,410 --> 00:33:52,040
是的 警官
Yes, sir.

571
00:33:52,080 --> 00:33:54,450
走
Let's move.

572
00:33:58,490 --> 00:34:00,920
绝对不能有任何人离开这艘船 明白吗?
Absolutely no one gets off this ship, understand?

573
00:34:00,950 --> 00:34:02,250
是的 警官
Yes, sir.

574
00:34:16,940 --> 00:34:18,640
我不认识什么肯尼尔·奥提斯
I don't know any Kaniel Outis.

575
00:34:18,670 --> 00:34:19,900
那家伙叫斯科菲尔德
The guy's name is Scofield.

576
00:34:19,940 --> 00:34:21,170
我好多年没见过他了
Haven't seen him in years.

577
00:34:21,210 --> 00:34:23,210
他打给我 他说他要搭船
He calls me, he says he needs a ride.

578
00:34:23,240 --> 00:34:26,180
我们在引擎舱进行追捕
We got active pursuit on engine deck.

579
00:34:26,210 --> 00:34:27,340
看着他
Watch him.

580
00:34:27,380 --> 00:34:29,910
那个人是叫斯科菲尔德!
The guy's name is Scofield!

581
00:34:33,520 --> 00:34:36,250
苏克雷说的那扇门
That's the door Sucre told us about.

582
00:34:37,160 --> 00:34:38,520
他们在那!
There they are!

583
00:34:38,560 --> 00:34:40,220
别动! 别动!
Freeze! Freeze!

584
00:34:41,760 --> 00:34:43,660
还活着
Look alive

585
00:34:43,700 --> 00:34:45,700
我们包围他们了
We've got them bottled up.

586
00:34:45,730 --> 00:34:48,500
大伙 快! 快点!
Guys, come on! Hurry!

587
00:34:48,530 --> 00:34:49,600
快!
Hurry!

588
00:34:49,640 --> 00:34:50,770
卡住了!
It's stuck!

589
00:34:50,800 --> 00:34:52,200
- 快点! - 门卡住了!
- Come on! - ‭It's stuck!

590
00:34:52,240 --> 00:34:54,300
卡住了!
It's stuck!

591
00:34:54,340 --> 00:34:55,710
熏他们出来 去!
Smoke them out, go!

592
00:35:07,090 --> 00:35:09,590
催泪弹
Tear gas.

593
00:35:09,620 --> 00:35:13,190
那会进入通风系统 会毁了我的船的
That hits the ventilation, it's gonna ruin my cargo.

594
00:35:16,160 --> 00:35:18,260
你就是个失败的人 苏克雷
You've always been a loser, Sucre.

595
00:35:18,300 --> 00:35:19,600
我雇过最糟的船员
Worst shipmate I ever hired.

596
00:35:19,630 --> 00:35:21,270
你把这趟破事带到我的船上
You brought this scum on board my ship.

597
00:35:21,300 --> 00:35:23,100
他们是你的朋友 他们要去哪里?
They're your friends. Where are they going?

598
00:35:23,140 --> 00:35:24,230
他们是朋友的朋友
They're associates of associates.

599
00:35:24,270 --> 00:35:26,140
我好多年没见过他们了
I haven't seen them in years.

600
00:35:26,170 --> 00:35:27,470
不过这让我想到了些事
But that's a good point.

601
00:35:27,510 --> 00:35:30,010
不如你告诉这些友好的海豹队员
Why don't you tell the nice SEAL here

602
00:35:30,040 --> 00:35:32,240
你是怎样收下他们的好处 让他们上船的?
how you accepted payment for their passage?

603
00:35:37,150 --> 00:35:39,780
可能他们是你的朋友 不是我的
Maybe they're your friends, not mine.

604
00:35:39,820 --> 00:35:41,990
好了 好了
Okay, okay.

605
00:35:42,020 --> 00:35:45,590
我听他们提到了十七号货仓
I heard them say something about container 17.

606
00:35:52,500 --> 00:35:54,830
十七号货仓
That container 17.

607
00:35:54,870 --> 00:35:58,700
你那个超级秘密的货仓是吧?
The one with your super secret cargo, huh?

608
00:35:58,740 --> 00:36:00,200
武器和弹药?
Weapons and munitions?

609
00:36:00,240 --> 00:36:03,440
文森特 船队可能也有武装
Vincent, tangos may be arming themselves.

610
00:36:03,480 --> 00:36:06,380
他们找到那些东西的话应该就不会喜欢你了吧 老兄
Man, they're not gonna like you if they find that, are they?

611
00:36:06,410 --> 00:36:08,080
文森特
Vincent.

612
00:36:08,110 --> 00:36:10,710
你可能也会被列到恐怖分子怀疑名单上
You might just end up on the terrorist watch list, too.

613
00:36:10,750 --> 00:36:11,720
文森特 收到吗?
Vincent, do you copy?

614
00:36:11,750 --> 00:36:13,650
听不清
Can't read you.

615
00:36:13,690 --> 00:36:17,520
没用的墨西哥佬 你都计划好的
Good-for-nothing Mexican. You planned this.

616
00:36:17,560 --> 00:36:18,690
留在这
Stay here.

617
00:36:27,570 --> 00:36:29,200
十七号还封着
17's still sealed.

618
00:36:33,410 --> 00:36:34,740
船长?
Captain?

619
00:36:37,810 --> 00:36:40,380
我可是波多黎各人
I'm Puerto Rican.

620
00:36:44,350 --> 00:36:46,720
12点钟方向 你听到了吗?
twelve o' clock ,You hear that?

621
00:36:53,860 --> 00:36:55,090
快来!
Come on!

622
00:37:00,750 --> 00:37:02,040
快 快 快走
Go, go. Move!

623
00:37:06,680 --> 00:37:08,000
出什么事了
What's going on?

624
00:37:08,020 --> 00:37:08,970
这条船正在改变航向
The ship's changing course.

625
00:37:11,200 --> 00:37:12,830
我做到了 兄弟
I did it, papi.

626
00:37:12,860 --> 00:37:14,270
现在回不了头了
No going back now.

627
00:37:15,710 --> 00:37:18,710
看看他们下一步要干什么吧
See what their next move is.

628
00:37:31,420 --> 00:37:34,290
你还记得我们的蜜月吗
Do you remember our honeymoon?

629
00:37:38,930 --> 00:37:40,730
记得 当然了
Yeah, of course.

630
00:37:40,770 --> 00:37:42,700
你向我敞开心扉
How you opened up.

631
00:37:42,730 --> 00:37:46,470
告诉我你为在狐狸河监狱的作为感到羞愧
Told me you carried shame for what you did at Fox River.

632
00:37:46,510 --> 00:37:49,740
告诉我你有时希望自己
How some days you wished you'd never heard

633
00:37:49,780 --> 00:37:51,940
从没听过迈克尔·斯科菲尔德这个名字
the name Michael Scofield.

634
00:37:53,910 --> 00:37:56,210
甚至承认你说谎了
Even admitted to lying,

635
00:37:56,250 --> 00:37:58,380
你之前把一切都瞒着我
keeping it all from me.

636
00:37:58,420 --> 00:38:01,500
还告诉我你最终如何清白脱身
How you finally came clean

637
00:38:01,580 --> 00:38:03,790
把一切抛之脑后
and put it all behind you?

638
00:38:05,490 --> 00:38:07,260
我记得
Sure.

639
00:38:07,290 --> 00:38:10,430
我原谅了你的谎言
I forgave you for the lies.

640
00:38:10,460 --> 00:38:12,600
你的过去
Your past.

641
00:38:12,630 --> 00:38:14,330
我接受了你
Accepted you.

642
00:38:14,370 --> 00:38:16,470
爱你 也爱迈克
Loved you and Mike.

643
00:38:16,500 --> 00:38:18,500
难道这对你来说还不够吗
How is that not enough for you?

644
00:38:35,550 --> 00:38:36,790
嗨
Hi.

645
00:38:36,820 --> 00:38:37,950
你好
Hello?

646
00:38:37,990 --> 00:38:39,620
我接到他了
I have him.

647
00:38:39,660 --> 00:38:42,290
谢天谢地
Thank God.

648
00:38:42,330 --> 00:38:43,890
他很好
He's fine.

649
00:38:43,930 --> 00:38:45,460
正往我家走呢
Headed home now.

650
00:38:45,500 --> 00:38:46,700
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.

651
00:38:46,730 --> 00:38:49,430
哦 海瑟 太谢谢你了
Oh, Heather, thank God.

652
00:38:49,470 --> 00:38:51,630
我马上就到
I'll be there soon.

653
00:39:34,580 --> 00:39:37,000
导航仪被毁了
Navigation's been trashed,

654
00:39:37,040 --> 00:39:39,140
控制器也坏了
the controls damaged.

655
00:39:41,210 --> 00:39:42,480
妈的
Damn it.

656
00:39:42,510 --> 00:39:44,110
货船偏离航向了
Tramp's off course.

657
00:39:44,150 --> 00:39:47,050
正在向阿尔及利亚水域全速航行
Moving toward Algerian waters, top speed.

658
00:39:47,080 --> 00:39:48,480
我们能修好吗
Can we fix it?

659
00:39:48,520 --> 00:39:49,550
那要花时间
It'll take time.

660
00:39:49,590 --> 00:39:50,700
估计到时候
And by then we'd be out

661
00:39:50,800 --> 00:39:51,940
我们就出了公海了
of international waters.

662
00:39:52,390 --> 00:39:55,420
猎鹰一号请求指令
Falcon One requesting orders.

663
00:39:55,460 --> 00:39:58,430
我们出了状况
We have a situation.

664
00:40:00,200 --> 00:40:01,630
说
Yeah.

665
00:40:01,660 --> 00:40:03,900
海豹突击队没能拿下奥提斯
The SEAL team failed to neutralize Outis.

666
00:40:03,930 --> 00:40:06,260
不知为何船的控制仪被毁了
Somehow the ship's controls were damaged.

667
00:40:06,340 --> 00:40:07,620
现在正往阿尔及利亚水域前行
It's headed for Algerian waters

668
00:40:07,680 --> 00:40:09,340
我们的士兵还在船上
with our soldiers on boards,

669
00:40:09,370 --> 00:40:10,900
但如果他们接着在船上狙杀他们
but it'll cause a diplomatic incident

670
00:40:10,940 --> 00:40:13,240
就会引起外交事故了
if they stay to finish the job.

671
00:40:13,280 --> 00:40:15,710
海军那边刚刚打电话暂停了行动
The navy just made the call to pull the team.

672
00:40:15,740 --> 00:40:17,310
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.

673
00:40:17,350 --> 00:40:19,210
海豹突击队完成不了 我们就升级行动
The SEALs couldn't do it. We escalate our move.

674
00:40:19,250 --> 00:40:21,150
就不该带把刀去参加枪战
Shouldn't have brought a knife to a gunfight.

675
00:40:21,180 --> 00:40:22,720
接下来我来处理 谢谢
I will handle from here. Thank you.

676
00:40:36,770 --> 00:40:37,860
长官
Sir.

677
00:40:37,900 --> 00:40:39,370
请讲
Yes.

678
00:40:39,400 --> 00:40:42,300
我有一个请求 一个紧急请求
I have an ask, one that's imperative.

679
00:40:42,340 --> 00:40:45,510
我想你会发现我们的利益是一致的
I believe you'll find that our interests are aligned.

680
00:41:00,860 --> 00:41:02,260
他们在干什么
What are they doing?

681
00:41:02,290 --> 00:41:03,260
他们在撤退
They're leaving.

682
00:41:03,290 --> 00:41:04,590
为什么
Why?

683
00:41:04,630 --> 00:41:05,760
快跑!
Run!

684
00:41:05,790 --> 00:41:08,860
哦 天啊 不 不 不 不!
Oh, God. No, no, no, no!

685
00:41:11,320 --> 00:41:13,130
嘿 你会需要这个的
Hey! You're gonna want this.

686
00:41:44,070 --> 00:41:47,230
迈克在安全地点 你动不了他 这一切都结束了
Mike is safe where you can't touch him, and this is over.

687
00:41:48,340 --> 00:41:51,400
我们的生活 所有谎言和伪装
The life, the lies, the mask.

688
00:41:51,440 --> 00:41:54,140
你要告诉我这一切的真相
You're gonna tell me everything.

689
00:41:54,180 --> 00:41:56,480
比如你到底是谁
Like who you really are,

690
00:41:56,510 --> 00:41:59,580
这到底怎么回事 我要你全盘托出
what this was, all of it.

691
00:41:59,620 --> 00:42:03,480
这就是我们的生活
It was our life.

692
00:42:03,520 --> 00:42:05,620
这一切并没有结束 莎拉
It's not over, Sara.

693
00:42:05,650 --> 00:42:08,390
还差得远呢
Not even close.

694
00:42:08,420 --> 00:42:10,460
迈克也从未陷入过险境
And Mike was never in danger.

695
00:42:10,540 --> 00:42:12,000
我爱他
I love him.

696
00:42:12,460 --> 00:42:14,960
他是我的家人
He is my family.

697
00:42:15,120 --> 00:42:17,200
我养育了他
I raised him.

698
00:42:17,280 --> 00:42:18,620
你做了什么
What have you done?

699
00:42:18,860 --> 00:42:23,740
不 是你做了什么 莎拉
No. It's what you've done, Sara.

700
00:42:23,770 --> 00:42:27,610
这一切本可以避免
All of this could've been avoided.

701
00:42:29,510 --> 00:42:30,780
在朋友家睡得好吗
Good sleepover?

702
00:42:30,810 --> 00:42:31,810
还好
Yeah.

703
00:42:31,850 --> 00:42:33,450
妈妈会来接我吗
Is Mommy coming to pick me up?

704
00:42:33,480 --> 00:42:36,020
会的 少爷
Yes, sir.

705
00:42:37,390 --> 00:42:40,390
迈克尔已经死了
Michael's dead.

706
00:42:40,420 --> 00:42:43,560
你的希腊南丁格尔之行直接领我找到了他
Your Nightingale trip to Greece led me straight to him.

707
00:42:45,030 --> 00:42:48,560
所以... 这都是你造成的 莎拉
So... it's all on you, Sara.

708
00:42:48,600 --> 00:42:51,900
你让海瑟帮忙的计划也是行不通的
And your plan with Heather didn't work.

709
00:42:51,930 --> 00:42:54,170
我儿子在哪
Where's my son?

710
00:42:54,200 --> 00:42:55,300
在我手里
I have him.

711
00:42:56,540 --> 00:42:58,210
至于我是不是必须得威胁他...
And whether or not I have to threaten him...

712
00:42:58,240 --> 00:43:00,140
虽然我并不想这么做
which I don't want to do...

713
00:43:00,180 --> 00:43:03,840
完全取决于你是否会把枪放下
is entirely contingent upon you putting the gun down.

714
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:30,000
{\fn锐字工房光芒黑简1.0\fs20\move(300,10,10,10)\an7\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}电影淘淘
{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\move(300,10,10,10)\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}WWW.{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\1c&H0080FF&\b0\i1}DYTTBD.COM

715
00:00:30,000 --> 02:00:00,000
{\fn锐字工房光芒黑简1.0\fs20\pos(10,10)\an7\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}电影淘淘
{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\pos(10,10)\1c&H6524FD&\b0\i1}WWW.{\fn微软雅黑\fs9\an7\1c&H0080FF&\b0\i1}DYTTBD.COM

716
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:15,000
{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&H6D04FB&\b0}更多电影美剧尽在（{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&HE6E600&\b0}电影淘淘 www.dyttbd.com{\fn汉仪晓波美妍体w\fs16\1c&H6D04FB&\b0}）
